<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JHN on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/jhn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JHN on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 02:41:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/jhn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JHN 3</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 02:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/3/</guid>
      <description>JHN 3:6 we are born of the flesh to enter into the Kingdom of this world and likewise we must be born of the spirit to enter into the Kingdom of God.
Just as we don&amp;rsquo;t know how bones are formed in the womb of a woman, likewise we don&amp;rsquo;t know how one is born of the Spirit.
Related verses: Ecclesiastes 11:5, John 3:5-8. See notes
JHN 3:17 God has always given man a second chance before initiating a final judgement as we can see in the times of Noah, the Judges, Lot etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 10</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 08:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/10/</guid>
      <description>JHN 10:10 The true state of a shepherd-sheep relationship. The real shepherd interceded on behalf of the sheep while the other sought to destroy the life of the child as she destroyed the life of her son.
The thief comes to kill, steal and destroy. Jesus came that we may have life.
The word of God is important in discerning good and wise judgement.
this is what happens when Satan brings an accusation before the father but Jesus or his followers petitions the father so that they might not be given over to the will of Satan the evil one</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 15</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 13:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/15/</guid>
      <description>JHN 15:25 Jesus was hated without a cause fulfilling this scripture
Related verses: Psalms 38:19, John 15:25. See notes
JHN 15:4 The secret to bearing much fruit is remaining in Christ and consistency I.e. continue to bear fruit and you will be pruned,
To stay fresh as a river, you need to flow continually. To be good at praying, you need to pray continually.
Related verses: JOHN 15:2, JOHN 15:4-5. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 12:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/4/</guid>
      <description>JHN 4:10 In God&amp;rsquo;s light our eyes are clear to behold light itself. God&amp;rsquo;s light gives us illumination
Related verses: Psalms 36:9, John 4:10, John 4:14. See notes
JHN 4:36  Doing the will of the father is God&amp;rsquo;s work Don&amp;rsquo;t think you have long time. Do it now. Don&amp;rsquo;t delay your blessings. The grace of God had power to do anything (only in the church can a somebody kneel down to a nobody to lay hands on them) Young people can be encouraged to do so much Part of church blessings is that you have friends Obedience is the key God uses people from a early age no matter who you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 14</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 07:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/14/</guid>
      <description>JHN 14:26 A good shepherd causes fear to disappear in the life of the sheep because they can confidently trust in him to lead them safely. He comforts them (The Holy ghost, the comforter)
The Holy Spirit is our teacher (who leads), comforter (whose rod protects) and whose staff (teaches and guides) us. The Holy Spirit is a great shepherd
Related verses: Psalms 23:4, John 14:26, John 16:13-14. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 16</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 07:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/16/</guid>
      <description>JHN 16:14 A good shepherd causes fear to disappear in the life of the sheep because they can confidently trust in him to lead them safely. He comforts them (The Holy ghost, the comforter)
The Holy Spirit is our teacher (who leads), comforter (whose rod protects) and whose staff (teaches and guides) us. The Holy Spirit is a great shepherd
Related verses: Psalms 23:4, John 14:26, John 16:13-14. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 05:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/6/</guid>
      <description>JHN 6:35 Bread gives strength because it is food. it satisfies hunger. Jesus satisfies our spiritual hunger because we are all hungry for something
Related verses: John 6:35. See notes
JHN 6:2 People flock to where their needs are met. Taiwo you need to be someone who meets the needs of others.
Miraculous signs like healing the sick will draw people. It is the anointing at work
Related verses: John 6:2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 22:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/1/</guid>
      <description>JHN 1:3  The word of a person are what we hear as they speak, the sound that comes from their mouth as they speak. This is a glimpse of a physical representation of the relation between Christ Jesus and our Heavenly Father as they are in the spiritual realm.  Related verses: John 1:1-3. See notes
JHN 1:32 The baptism was a way to identify Jesus as the messiah. Whoever the Holy Spirit falls and remains upon was the sign to be used to identify the messiah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 07:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/2/</guid>
      <description>JHN 2:2 Jesus already had disciples when he was invited to the wedding in Cana where he turned the water used for cleansing to wine for drinking and pleasure.
Imagine trying to use water to wash and find wine and you put some in your mouth and it tastes even nicer.
God provided more than enough. Had Jesus not been invited, there would have been shortage of wine.
It looks like it was a great feast and feasts usually lasts 7 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 12</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/12/</guid>
      <description>JHN 12:26 If I faithfully serve Jesus, the father will honour me
Related verses: John 12:26. See notes
JHN 12:11 They were expecting the Messiah yet were so obsessed with the teaching and traditions of the elders. They valued the oral changing traditions of the dead elders to the written unchanging word of the living God.
Related verses: John 12:11. See notes
JHN 12:10 The chief priests must be possessed to think of killing someone even though the scriptures says THOU SHALL NOT MURDER.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 21</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 07:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/21/</guid>
      <description>JHN 21:24 The author of this gospel, John was born in 6AD making him 11 years younger than Jesus. He was 19 when Jesus began his ministry.
Related verses: JOHN 21:24. See notes
JHN 21:11 They had toiled al night to catch a single fish but at one command from Jesus and obedience, they caught more than they were able to carry.
It was until Jesus appeared and spoke that miracles happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 9</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/9/</guid>
      <description>JHN 9:14 The sabbath was a day of rest not a day of burdens. A day of freedom not a day of religious exercise.
Jesus freed the man on sabbath as much as he did miracles most of the time on the sabbath.
Jesus himself is our sabbath.
?Come to me all that labour and are heavy laden and I will give you rest?
Related verses: JOHN 9:14. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 8</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 10:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/8/</guid>
      <description>JHN 8:58 I am the one who is the Lord. I am Yahweh
That?s why they wanted to stone him because they considered it blasphemy.
Related verses: JOHN 8:58. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 7</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 09:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/7/</guid>
      <description>JHN 7:39 The people were saved but hadn&amp;rsquo;t yet received the Holy Spirit. The Holy Spirit was then poured out on the day of Pentecost after Jesus had been raised to honour at the right hand of the father.
Related verses: JOHN 7:39. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JHN 13</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 22:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jhn/13/</guid>
      <description>JHN 13:18 I believe this Psalm was written when he fled from his son Absalom. His trusted friend and counsellor &amp;ldquo;Ahithophel&amp;rdquo; had connived with Absalom in his rebellion. Ahithophel&amp;rsquo;s motive may have been because David slept with his grand daughter &amp;ldquo;BathSheba&amp;rdquo; and had his son&amp;rsquo;s son-in-law Uriah killed in battle.
In those days, Ahithophel&amp;rsquo;s counsel was such that it was likened to when one inquired at the oracles of God (2 Samuel 16:23).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
