<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>REV on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/rev/</link>
    <description>Recent content in REV on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 09:24:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/rev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>REV 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/rev/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 09:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/rev/6/</guid>
      <description>REV 6:6 War, natural disasters and famine are signs and instruments of God&amp;rsquo;s judgement. When Jesus breaks open the seal, they will begin to manifest and we can already see
Related verses: Mark 13:8, Revelation 6:1-8. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REV 20</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/rev/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 10:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/rev/20/</guid>
      <description>REV 20:12 There is no reproduction in heaven. Angels don&amp;rsquo;t marry. When they rise from the dead? We know that not everyone has risen from the dead except for Jesus because everyone else who was raised from the dead died again. We are still awaiting our ressurected body.
This means that all dead people are still somewhere but not in heaven. Probably Hades but in the part of paradise awaiting ressurection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REV 13</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/rev/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 10:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/rev/13/</guid>
      <description>REV 13:11 That is a false Christ. The Antichrist
Related verses: REVELATION 13:11. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REV 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/rev/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 17:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/rev/2/</guid>
      <description>REV 2:5 Remembrance, repentance and doing the old works when we first met God is returning to the First Love.
Disobeying and not doing it is to lose your place and significance and the dream and purpose for which a God placed you where you were meant to be.
Related verses: REVELATION 2:5. See notes
REV 2:26 Believing, obedience, persistence and patience will enable me to have authority over the nations</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REV 18</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/rev/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 19:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/rev/18/</guid>
      <description>REV 18:3 Babylon was once great
(Babylon was handsome, he had 6 packs, he was built. He had muscles But he fell and is now the hold of every foul spirit and a cage of every unclean and hateful birds.)
If you have multiple sexual partners, you will become the habitation of Devils.
When you have sexual demons enter you, you become disobedient, licentious, rebellious.
Related verses: Revelation 18:2-5. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
