<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LEV on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/lev/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LEV on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:10:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/lev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LEV 11</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/11/</guid>
      <description>LEV 11:3 The progression from Genesis 2 where God created man and animals and instructed them to eat plants until their fall.
After the flood, some plants would have taken time to develop but God now accepted me San to eat of any and every animal not mentioning clean or unclean until the time of Moses.
How did Noah know the clean and unclean animals to pick because we only found out about it in exodus but Abraham had already been sacrificing clean animals even in the time of Abel they probably knew what was clean and unclean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEV 16</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 16:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/16/</guid>
      <description>LEV 16:13 the purpose of the incense and the fire was to create a cloud of smoke which would then cover the mercy seat so that the high priest would not come into direct eye contact with God when he sprinkles the blood on the mercy seat. this is because the glory of God will be manifested
Related verses: Leviticus 16:2, Leviticus 16:13. See notes
LEV 16:15 The High priest was to offer two sacrifices on the day of atonement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEV 14</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 12:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/14/</guid>
      <description>LEV 14:36 The house must be emptied before the priest comes in otherwise they will all be declared unclean. This means that as long as the priest has not entered, there is still grace to save some. The priest represented God to the people and because he carried the anointing, the anointing has not entered the unclean house
Related verses: Leviticus 14:36. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEV 10</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 08:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/10/</guid>
      <description>LEV 10:9 I think Aaron?s sons may have been under the influence of alcohol when they went to offer fire to God. It may have impaired their ability to think properly. In this scenario, they were setting a bad example and if God had not intervened, the people would have thought it was normal.
Related verses: Leviticus 10:9. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEV 8</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 15:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/8/</guid>
      <description>LEV 8:17 The sin offering was always to be burned because it signified impurity. It had to be burned so that none would remain thereby an example of sinlessness and perfect purity
Related verses: Leviticus 8:17. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEV 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 07:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/6/</guid>
      <description>LEV 6:30 No offering whose blood is used to make atonement must be eaten. It must be completely devoted to God
Related verses: Leviticus 6:30. See notes
LEV 6:5 All these just because of stealing. Then it is better not to steal lol
Related verses: Leviticus 6:4-6. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEV 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 09:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/4/</guid>
      <description>LEV 4:3 The high priest represented the whole congregations therefore for the anointed priest to sin was tantamount to the whole Israelites sinning.
Only the anointed priest and the whole congregation were told to sacrifice a bull. The sacrifice was costly depending on the status of the sinner.
 bull for High priest/whole congregation make goat for Civic leader female goat/lamb for ordinary Israelite turtle dove/pigeon for the very poor handful of fine flour for the too poor  For offerings of an animal, it had to be without blemish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEV 26</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 12:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/lev/26/</guid>
      <description>LEV 26:16 Disobedience to God brings poverty, sickness, terror, fear and death
Related verses: Leviticus 26:16. See notes
LEV 26:9 You gain God&amp;rsquo;s respect and blessings when you obey him
Related verses: Leviticus 26:9. See notes
LEV 26:34 This is where Daniel got his revelation about when they would be free from exile (70 years)
When there is the shedding of innocent blood and idolatry, judgement is soon to come.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
