<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PRO on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/pro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PRO on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 08:42:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/pro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PRO 29</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 08:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/29/</guid>
      <description>PRO 29:14 Jesus modelled this example and his throne has been established forever.
Related verses: Proverbs 29:14, Luke 4:18. See notes
PRO 29:11 It is foolishness to be quick tempered. I must learn to exercise self control
Related verses: Proverbs 29:11. See notes
PRO 29:7 A righteous man has concerns for the poor
Related verses: Proverbs 29:7. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 10</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 05:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/10/</guid>
      <description>PRO 10:22 The blessings of the Lord makes rich. It always increase
Related verses: Genesis 1:28, Proverbs 10:22, Isaiah 51:2. See notes
PRO 10:22 the blessings of God makes rich and there is no sorrow attached
Related verses: Proverbs 10:22, Ecclesiastes 5:19. See notes
PRO 10:29 Defence or ruin? it depends on me to choose the way of God or not
Related verses: Proverbs 10:29. See notes
PRO 10:26 very irritating</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 30</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 10:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/30/</guid>
      <description>PRO 30:4 Similarities in both verses and Jesus fulfilled the calming of the storm and rebuking the wind. He also walked on water
Related verses: Proverbs 30:4-5, Isaiah 40:12. See notes
PRO 30:18 It has no tracks that can be followed
Related verses: Proverbs 30:18-19. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 27</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 08:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/27/</guid>
      <description>PRO 27:18 Honour begets honour
Related verses: Proverbs 27:18. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 26</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 08:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/26/</guid>
      <description>PRO 26:20 for lack of wood the fire goes out. when sacrifice and dying to self ends, the fire of the Holy Spirit goes out and I become a cold Christian
Related verses: Proverbs 26:20. See notes
PRO 26:10 everything must be thoughtful and calculated
Related verses: Proverbs 26:10. See notes
PRO 26:12 This chapter has been talking about the negativity of foolishness and how it can greatly damage a person&amp;rsquo;s reputation, ideas and progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 25</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 08:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/25/</guid>
      <description>PRO 25:25 very refreshing
Related verses: Proverbs 25:25. See notes
PRO 25:19 painful and unreliable
Related verses: Proverbs 25:19. See notes
PRO 25:4 All sins needs to be repented before God can use me. I need to walk in righteousness and holiness
Related verses: Proverbs 25:4, 2 Timothy 2:21. See notes
PRO 25:2 Deep search. There are a lot of things hidden by God and those who dig deep into God gets the treasure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 24</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/24/</guid>
      <description>PRO 24:18 Even though God wants to fight for me. if he sees me rejoicing over my enemy when they fall, he will be displeased and won&amp;rsquo;t take action anymore because the fee had been paid by my rejoicing at the fall of my enemy
Related verses: Proverbs 24:17-18. See notes
PRO 24:11 there&amp;rsquo;s nothing like it&amp;rsquo;s none of my business
Related verses: Proverbs 24:11-12. See notes
PRO 24:5 When it comes to God, it&amp;rsquo;s not about strength but wisdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 23</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 12:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/23/</guid>
      <description>PRO 23:27 A trap and a highway to hell and the grave
Related verses: Proverbs 23:27. See notes
PRO 23:21 Poverty is to a glutton and a drunkard
Related verses: Proverbs 23:20-21. See notes
PRO 23:11 God will personally fight for the fatherless and the poor and the widow
Related verses: Proverbs 23:10-11. See notes
PRO 23:33 Getting drunk is closely connected to fornication/adultery because you lose your essence of self-control and that can give demons the right to work in, with or on you</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 22</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 11:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/22/</guid>
      <description>PRO 22:29 the value of skill
Related verses: Proverbs 22:29. See notes
PRO 22:22 God is careful about the poor. they must not be oppressed otherwise he will tlrose to fight those who do
Related verses: Proverbs 22:22-23. See notes
PRO 22:16 God does not joke with the poor. Opressing or exploiting the poor leads to curses but giving to the poor leads to blessings.
Related verses: Proverbs 22:16. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 21</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 05:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/21/</guid>
      <description>PRO 21:13 Anyone who ignores the poor would suffer. it said he himself would CRY then he would not be heard.
If I love the lord and my neighbour, I&amp;rsquo;ll definitely give to the poor
Related verses: Proverbs 21:13, Matthew 5:42. See notes
PRO 21:23 Your mouth and what you say determines the course of your life
Related verses: PROVERBS 21:23. See notes
PRO 21:22 Wisdom is better than strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 20</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 05:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/20/</guid>
      <description>PRO 20:26 The threshing wheel separates the chaff from the wheat by subjecting the grain to pressure when it is treaded on by both the wheels and the cow threshing the grain.
Satan petitioned God to have Job sifted like wheat but Job&amp;rsquo;s faith did not fail. Satan demanded that Peter would be tested as well but his faith did not fail even when he denied Jesus and went back to fishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 19</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 08:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/19/</guid>
      <description>PRO 19:24 A sluggard can&amp;rsquo;t complete tasks
Related verses: Proverbs 19:24. See notes
PRO 19:19 I must learn self-control and not be driven by anger or quick temper
Related verses: Proverbs 19:19. See notes
PRO 19:5 A liar and a false witness are abomination to God and will never go unpunished
Related verses: PROVERBS 19:5. See notes
PRO 19:20 Counsel, instruction and correction are the elements on wisdom that grows with time</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 18</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 08:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/18/</guid>
      <description>PRO 18:24 Not everyone can be friends. the more friends I have, the easier it is to fall away from the true path
Related verses: Proverbs 18:24. See notes
PRO 18:21 tongues have power. they are ways by which the desire of the soul (thoughts of the mind, desires of the will and the feelings of the emotion) are expressed
Related verses: Proverbs 18:21. See notes
PRO 18:16 Giving a gift is a symbol of honour and that you thought about the person</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 17</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 08:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/17/</guid>
      <description>PRO 17:27 This is talking to me. I need to be careful with my words and I must be temperate and have self control. no need to be unnecessarily angry
Related verses: Proverbs 17:27. See notes
PRO 17:16 Common sense is needed to keep sound wisdom
Related verses: Proverbs 17:16. See notes
PRO 17:14 words of wisdom. no need to waste time fighting
Related verses: Proverbs 17:14. See notes
PRO 17:13 Lord have mercy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 16</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 05:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/16/</guid>
      <description>PRO 16:7 God is the author of peace. Fearing and pleasing God causes peace to abound on all sides. Example was Solomon before his fall
Related verses: Proverbs 16:7. See notes
PRO 16:6 If I want to depart from evil, I must reverence God and this is God&amp;rsquo;s wisdom and greatness in God&amp;rsquo;s sight. An example is Job who feared God and shunned evil and was described as the greatest of the men of the east.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 15</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 04:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/15/</guid>
      <description>PRO 15:33 Humility and the fear of the Lord is the key to wisdom and honour. these generates riches, honour and life
Related verses: Proverbs 15:33, Proverbs 22:4. See notes
PRO 15:32 Learning from rebukes is the key to change. People can see about me what I can&amp;rsquo;t see about myself so I need to be willing to listen to them otherwise I don&amp;rsquo;t love myself.
Accepting correction helps me in acquiring wisdom</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 14</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 05:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/14/</guid>
      <description>PRO 14:33 wisdomis of the heart and wisdom comes wge there is understanding of a particular subject matter
Related verses: Proverbs 14:33. See notes
PRO 14:31 giving and showing mercy to the poor is a way to honour God
Related verses: Proverbs 14:31. See notes
PRO 14:4 there&amp;rsquo;s got to be some bad to achieve something good. I can&amp;rsquo;t eat my cake and have it. Anybody will have both good and bad character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 13</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 10:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/13/</guid>
      <description>PRO 13:20 Who are my company. I am influenced by my company
Related verses: Proverbs 13:20. See notes
PRO 13:18 Anyone who is poor is proud because he refuses instruction and discipline
Related verses: Proverbs 13:18. See notes
PRO 13:13 Despise or respect destruction or reward
I have to choose to obey God to be rewarded
Related verses: Proverbs 13:13. See notes
PRO 13:11 The key is gathering in crumbs through honesty</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 12</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 12:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/12/</guid>
      <description>PRO 12:27 diligence and opportunity. knowing the right time and taking the chance
Related verses: Proverbs 12:27. See notes
PRO 12:25 I must learn to be an encourager.
Related verses: Proverbs 12:25. See notes
PRO 12:24 Diligence makes a leader. Lazy and negligent people are subjected to servitude
Related verses: Proverbs 12:24. See notes
PRO 12:23 even a wise man has the proper time to speak
Related verses: Proverbs 12:23. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 11</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 10:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/11/</guid>
      <description>PRO 11:29 A wise man is prone to becoming a leader while a foolish man can only be subjected to service
Related verses: Proverbs 11:29. See notes
PRO 11:25 Generosity is a seed that will bring returns in the future.
Related verses: Proverbs 11:25. See notes
PRO 11:15 I must not be a guarantor for anyone otherwise I&amp;rsquo;ll suffer terribly from the consequence
Related verses: Proverbs 11:15. See notes
PRO 11:30 Righteousness saves you from eternal condemnation and by winning souls, you gather up rewards for eternity with God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 9</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 05:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/9/</guid>
      <description>PRO 9:12 At the end of the day, I real the benefits of my choice whether to choose God&amp;rsquo;s wisdom or not
Related verses: Proverbs 9:12. See notes
PRO 9:11 Divine Wisdom prolongs life and gives vigour and energy and strengtg to my life
Related verses: Proverbs 9:11. See notes
PRO 9:10 Knowledge of God is important because it gives is the understanding to know God and once we know God, we can truly learn how to reverence him (then comes wisdom through the reverence).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 8</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 15:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/8/</guid>
      <description>PRO 8:14 The woman personified as wisdom is the Holy Spirit. The spirit of counsel, wisdom, understanding, power, knowledge as mentioned in Isaiah.
wisdom (The Holy Spirit) can provide everything I need. this wisdom personified as a woman was given to Jesus in full measure as seen in Isaiah 11:2.
the fruit of wisdom is better than silver or gold. the fruits of wisdom is love, joy, peace, patience, kindness, goodness and faithfulness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 7</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 11:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/7/</guid>
      <description>PRO 7:23 the same fate of the wicked. Adultery is also categorised as wickedness
Related verses: Job 20:24-25, Proverbs 7:23. See notes
PRO 7:26 What a great comparison between the Proverbs 7 woman e.g. Delilah and the Proverbs 31 woman e.g. Ruth
The Proverbs 7 woman is an immoral woman given to sensual pleasures. Her work is to seek out men who would satisfy her desire even though she was already married.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 12:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/6/</guid>
      <description>PRO 6:16  Just like Jesus wore the crown of thorns to save us from the wrath and abomination of our heavenly father,  A proud look stems from the heart because it is the attitude that overestimates oneself and discount others.
 Jesus suffered thirst from the tongue  the tongue speaks out lies, deceits and is the agent of false witnesses
 his hands were nailed to the cross his side were pierced (where his heart is located) his feets were pierced  Related verses: Proverbs 6:16-19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/5/</guid>
      <description>PRO 5:1 Why do I want to pay the price of the same costly experience when I can just learn from it and avoid pitfalls?
Related verses: Proverbs 5:1. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/4/</guid>
      <description>PRO 4:18 The way of the righteous keeps getting brighter and brighter whereas that of the wicked is like deep darkness
Related verses: Proverbs 4:18-19. See notes
PRO 4:10 If I want long life, I better take heed to the word of God
Related verses: Proverbs 4:10. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 3</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 01:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/3/</guid>
      <description>PRO 3:4 I find favour in the sight of God and man because of the three qualities: mercy, kindness and truth.
mercy and truth because God desires both and kindness in judgement will make me show compassion. God is full of compassion
Related verses: Proverbs 3:4. See notes
PRO 3:1 backsliding starts from the heart and that is why I must keep my heart with all diligence. I won&amp;rsquo;t forget the teachings of wisdom when I have rehearsed it continually until it becomes part of me</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 07:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/2/</guid>
      <description>PRO 2:1 Seeking the knowledge of God as if mining gold is the criteria to finding wisdom. it&amp;rsquo;s not easy to get treasures and neither is it easy to know God. only those who knows the value of knowing God will seek him.
once we find God, God willbimpart to us his wisdom because we seek him on the basis of his word and the more we know his word, the more we start to become acquainted with him and can know what steps to take if in a dilemma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 23:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/1/</guid>
      <description>PRO 1:5 continuous learning helps to renew my mind since ignorance is costly. I must be attentive to words especially by God.
the sign that I am wise is in learning and not just reading
Related verses: Proverbs 1:5. See notes
PRO 1:23 If I pay attention to the rebuke if God&amp;rsquo;s word, he will pour out the spirit of wisdom on me
Related verses: Proverbs 1:23. See notes
PRO 1:16 Advice against greed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRO 28</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 16:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/pro/28/</guid>
      <description>PRO 28:2 Knowledge and understanding ensures stability in a nation
Related verses: PROVERBS 28:2. See notes
PRO 28:27 The rewards of being generous is that more will keep coming. I am blessed to be a blessing to others.
Related verses: Proverbs 19:17, Proverbs 28:27. See notes
PRO 28:20 Impatience will bring disaster
Related verses: Proverbs 28:20. See notes
PRO 28:19 Hard work produced results
Related verses: Proverbs 28:19. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
