<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GEN on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/gen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GEN on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:10:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/gen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GEN 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/2/</guid>
      <description>GEN 2:16 The progression from Genesis 2 where God created man and animals and instructed them to eat plants until their fall.
After the flood, some plants would have taken time to develop but God now accepted me San to eat of any and every animal not mentioning clean or unclean until the time of Moses.
How did Noah know the clean and unclean animals to pick because we only found out about it in exodus but Abraham had already been sacrificing clean animals even in the time of Abel they probably knew what was clean and unclean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 7</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/7/</guid>
      <description>GEN 7:2 The progression from Genesis 2 where God created man and animals and instructed them to eat plants until their fall.
After the flood, some plants would have taken time to develop but God now accepted me San to eat of any and every animal not mentioning clean or unclean until the time of Moses.
How did Noah know the clean and unclean animals to pick because we only found out about it in exodus but Abraham had already been sacrificing clean animals even in the time of Abel they probably knew what was clean and unclean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 9</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/9/</guid>
      <description>GEN 9:3 The progression from Genesis 2 where God created man and animals and instructed them to eat plants until their fall.
After the flood, some plants would have taken time to develop but God now accepted me San to eat of any and every animal not mentioning clean or unclean until the time of Moses.
How did Noah know the clean and unclean animals to pick because we only found out about it in exodus but Abraham had already been sacrificing clean animals even in the time of Abel they probably knew what was clean and unclean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 05:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/1/</guid>
      <description>GEN 1:28 The blessings of the Lord makes rich. It always increase
Related verses: Genesis 1:28, Proverbs 10:22, Isaiah 51:2. See notes
GEN 1:30 Before the fall of man, the food given to mankind was every green plant and fruit-bearing tree with SEED in it. This islso brings to mind the notion of fruitfulness.
After the fall of man, eating animals was included but blood was forbidden.
Related verses: GENESIS 1:29-30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 12:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/6/</guid>
      <description>GEN 6:8 Noah found grace through faith. he was willing to believe against all odds that the prophecies of the flood was real and true and he took action
Related verses: Genesis 6:8, Ephesians 2:8-9, Hebrews 11:7. See notes
GEN 6:3 The Holy Spirit was trying to help man live right but man was given to lust of the flesh, lust of the eyes and the pride of life.
God had to take away his spirit and man died a total spiritual death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 19</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 19:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/19/</guid>
      <description>GEN 19:3 A sign of the communion. they had communion before judgement. Jesus had communion before he faced judgement on the cross. The Israelites had communion before judgement fell on Egypt.
The communion and the unleavened bread was to show that there is no sin in me and the wine is a sign of purity. After you crush me, you will find no dreggs in me.
But Jesus had to drink of the cup of God&amp;rsquo;s wrath and taste the dreggs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 35</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 22:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/35/</guid>
      <description>GEN 35:18 This event was a prophecy about Joseph?s future. Joseph experienced sorrow from his family to slavery in Egypt but he became the right hand man of Pharaoh at last. His life didn?t end in sorrow
Related verses: GENESIS 35:18. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 31</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 10:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/31/</guid>
      <description>GEN 31:15 There was also bride price in the time of Laban and Jacob. This custom has been since and is still practiced in many places especially in Africa.
Related verses: GENESIS 31:15. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 28</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 11:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/28/</guid>
      <description>GEN 28:22 A tithe is a sign of dependence on God. The stone as a pillar was a memorial of covenant between Jacob and God.
I perceive Jacob must have taken a stone that had previously been used as an altar. This is just a speculation
Related verses: GENESIS 28:22. See notes
GEN 28:12 Jacob saw a stairway to heaven with Angels descending and ascending on it and he named the place Beth-El (House of God).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 25</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 14:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/25/</guid>
      <description>GEN 25:31 Jacob must have thought a lot about the birthright or known a secret about it for him to just ask out of the blue to purchase birthright with a stew
Related verses: GENESIS 25:31. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 24</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 04:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/24/</guid>
      <description>GEN 24:65 It was customary to cover the bride with a veil before marriage as is still done in several cultures today.
likewise when we are married to Christ, the veil is removed and we begin to behold Christ.
I must not take my gaze away from Christ. The apostle Paul said in 2 Corinthians 3
14 But their minds were made dull, for to this day the same veil remains when the old covenant is read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 22</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 07:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/22/</guid>
      <description>GEN 22:18 Abraham became a blessing because he was obedient and didn&amp;rsquo;t withhold his son from God
Related verses: GENESIS 22:18. See notes
GEN 22:3 Abraham got up EARLY in the morning.
Early will I seek thee&amp;hellip; - Psalm 63
Related verses: GENESIS 22:3. See notes
GEN 22:12  To fear God is to obey him. To fear God is to not withhold anything from him. To fear God is to prevent anything from taking away what God demands from you  A three days journey without Abraham changing his mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 21</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 09:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/21/</guid>
      <description>GEN 21:33 Abraham was a man of prayer. He erected altars wherever he moved to. Even planting a tamarisk tree where he would go to pray
Related verses: GENESIS 21:33. See notes
GEN 21:6 Previously people had laughed about Sarah and called her barren but now her situation had been turned around by God and people had began laughing with her.
Related verses: GENESIS 21:6. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 20</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 16:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/20/</guid>
      <description>GEN 20:7 First mention of a prophet was in reference to Abraham. God answered Abraham&amp;rsquo;s prayer regarding this and was protective of Abraham even though he seemed to lie about his situation. (Although Sarah is his step sister turned wife)
Related verses: GENESIS 20:7. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 11:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/5/</guid>
      <description>GEN 5:24 Everyone God wrote and he died except Enoch because he walked with God 300 years
Related verses: GENESIS 5:24. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 11:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/4/</guid>
      <description>GEN 4:11 First cursed man because he murdered his brother. God cursed the ground because of Adam&amp;rsquo;s sins now God cursed Cain from the ground because of his sin.
Related verses: GENESIS 4:11. See notes
GEN 4:9 God&amp;rsquo;s resolve to sin is questioning. It is best I question myself before I am questioned by God.
The first recorded lie in the Bible is from Cain after he sinned.
The immediate impulse from sin was to forget about others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 3</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 10:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/3/</guid>
      <description>GEN 3:6 Adam was called Eve&amp;rsquo;s husband which means they had gotten married. so any notion of them having sex wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have been a sin.
This is for people who thinks the sin and the real forbidden fruit was having sex. that is untrue and unscriptural.
Related verses: GENESIS 3:6. See notes
GEN 3:22 It is God&amp;rsquo;s mercy that we were prevented from living forever in our fallen state because we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have been able to die since the wages of sin is death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 49</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/49/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 06:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/49/</guid>
      <description>GEN 49:13 The prophecy of Jacob came to pass in the lives of his children. We need to be careful about what we do to our parents so we don&amp;rsquo;t get cursed.
Related verses: GENESIS 49:13, MATTHEW 4:12. See notes
GEN 49:8 Judah lived up to his name. Even though he. Was the instrument behind Joseph&amp;rsquo;s slavery into Egypt, he was the first to be blessed among his brothers.
God used him for a greater blessing and the sceptre of rulership was passed on to him till Jesus comes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 11</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 02:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/11/</guid>
      <description>GEN 11:6 Unity brings great accomplishment.
Related verses: GENESIS 11:5-6, EZRA 3:1. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 41</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 04:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/41/</guid>
      <description>GEN 41:38 Joseph was wise and discreet because the Holy Spirit was in him. Because of this, he was lifted to a better position but before this, he had to pass through tests of obedience, faithfulness, hard work
Related verses: GENESIS 41:38-39. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 45</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/45/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 04:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/45/</guid>
      <description>GEN 45:11 Joseph was 39 years at this time
Related verses: GENESIS 45:11. See notes
GEN 45:8 Recognised that it was God&amp;rsquo;s will and not of his brothers to sell him into slavery.
God had a better plan. Previously God had told Abraham about what was gonna happen in the future that Israelites would be slaves in Egypt. This is how God&amp;rsquo;s plan would be fulfilled.
Related verses: Genesis 45:7-8. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 46</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/46/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 21:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/46/</guid>
      <description>GEN 46:4 Faith Even though Jacob knew his families were going to suffer in Egypt for 400+ years, he still obeyed God. Even though he didn&amp;rsquo;t live to witness those years of suffering nor did he get the inheritance in his lifetime, he still proceeded into Egypt with his family.
Sometimes, it is God&amp;rsquo;s will that we go through a very difficult time in our life. God has his plan and his reward but are we willing to trust him even though we don&amp;rsquo;t see the big picture or do we want to do it our own way and bear the consequences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN 44</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/44/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 11:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/gen/44/</guid>
      <description>GEN 44:33 Repentance What a transformation. The Judah that was behind selling Joseph as a slave in times past was now willing to be in place of Benjamin as a servant of Joseph. Great sign of repentance. The brothers of Joseph had come to realise that they acted foolishly are now regretting their past actions
When you repent, it shows in your actions and words
Related verses: Genesis 44:33. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
