<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EZK on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/ezk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in EZK on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 19:05:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/ezk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EZK 22</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/ezk/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 19:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/ezk/22/</guid>
      <description>EZK 22:4 God&amp;rsquo;s judgement was because of idolatry and bloodshed. A direct desecration of the golden rule. To love God and others.
Sodom and Gomorrah was involved in this. Homosexuality was a common practise in Sodom and Gomorrah. Male temple prostitutes also engaged in homosexual acts in pagan religion.
Before God judges the earth, there had to be an outcry by humans bringing into account the deeds of the offenders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EZK 40</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/ezk/40/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/ezk/40/</guid>
      <description>EZK 40:4 Lack of attention can cause a big problem
Related verses: EZEKIEL 40:4. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EZK 44</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/ezk/44/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 09:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/ezk/44/</guid>
      <description>EZK 44:23 The Levitical priests of God are sanctified and Holiness is transmitted to the people when they came in contact with the priest clothes that was used to serve God. God forbade that they should wear the clothes to serve the people. Instead, they should change there garments before ministering to the people.
They were also to teach the people the things of God. The Holy and unholy and also teach them to distinguish between the clean and the ceremonially unclean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EZK 36</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/ezk/36/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 09:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/ezk/36/</guid>
      <description>EZK 36:27 A new heart and a new spirit (The Holy Spirit will cause us to walk in the statutes of the living God) for we cannot really obey him of our own stony heart and spirit that is dead to God through sin
Related verses: EZEKIEL 36:27. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EZK 18</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/ezk/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 09:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/ezk/18/</guid>
      <description>EZK 18:32 What a gracious God. Our choice to live is in our hands.
Related verses: EZEKIEL 18:32. See notes
EZK 18:29 We still have people who try to judge God today. You who are full of wickedness, how can you define right and wrong for God.
Related verses: EZEKIEL 18:29. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
