<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LUK on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/luk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LUK on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 09:24:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/luk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LUK 18</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 09:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/18/</guid>
      <description>LUK 18:1 We can continue to call on God such that he is forced to give a response
Related verses: Isaiah 62:7, Luke 18:1-9. See notes
LUK 18:8 Persistence is directly related to how quick I receive your answers.
Persistent prayer is directly proportional to how much faith I have
Related verses: LUKE 18:8. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 23</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 09:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/23/</guid>
      <description>LUK 23:46 The spirit of man goes to heaven. The soul goes to hell, the body perishes on the earth
Related verses: Ecclesiastes 12:7, Luke 23:46, Acts 7:59. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 08:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/2/</guid>
      <description>LUK 2:35 The word of God as the sword of the spirit dividing the soul and the spirit to reveal the thoughts and intentions of the heart
Related verses: 1 Kings 3:24, 1 Kings 3:27-28, Luke 2:35, Hebrews 4:12. See notes
LUK 2:23 I believe the parents of Jesus were poor. The law said anyone who couldn&amp;rsquo;t afford a lamb to redeem the first son that opens the womb should offer a pair of turtle doves or two young pigeon (Leviticus 12:8) and that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what the parents of Jesus did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 12</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 16:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/12/</guid>
      <description>LUK 12:18 The soul is the entity that is judged and that which God requires.
Life and accomplishments and labours without God is vain and useless. God has made sure that we human are dependent beings on him and we cause ourselves problems when we decide to revel against him and live our own lives.
It debased us to live like mere animals as we are without God.
Related verses: Ecclesiastes 4:8, Luke 12:16-21.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 22</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 05:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/22/</guid>
      <description>LUK 22:31 The threshing wheel separates the chaff from the wheat by subjecting the grain to pressure when it is treaded on by both the wheels and the cow threshing the grain.
Satan petitioned God to have Job sifted like wheat but Job&amp;rsquo;s faith did not fail. Satan demanded that Peter would be tested as well but his faith did not fail even when he denied Jesus and went back to fishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 20</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 07:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/20/</guid>
      <description>LUK 20:4 Baptism is an agreement and outward sign and public declaration of an inner change of mind and heart. Because it is public, it is visible to the public and humbling because people will see you and will know you agree that you are a sinner.
it took humility to be baptised. Christ was humble enough to get baptised. John was baptised from heaven (ordained by God. he was filled with the Holy Spirit from birth).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 24</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 06:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/24/</guid>
      <description>LUK 24:45 Solomon prayed for an understanding mind and a hearing (obedient heart). Understanding is really important in administer justice as the King and representatives of God.
I as a Christian represent the Lord Jesus and need understanding to obey the words of God. Unless God opens my mind, I may never understand many things that I have been taught. Since my mind needs to be renewed by the word of God, it becomes easier when I pray for God to give me an understanding mind and an obedient heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 08:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/6/</guid>
      <description>LUK 6:19 This wasn?t even Jesus trying to pray for them. It is power coming from him and healing them as they tried to touch him
Related verses: Luke 6:19. See notes
LUK 6:7 There is usually a stronghold present when someone is filled with dos and donts. It?s usually a sign of bondage and oppression. Lack of the Holy Spirit .
On the other hand a lack of self control is also a sign of the presence of demons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 14:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/5/</guid>
      <description>LUK 5:33 That was an indirect insult to Jesus that he didn?t teach his disciples well and also since he was an irresponsible party goer it was clear that his disciples would be the same as well as his circles of sinners
Related verses: Luke 5:33. See notes
LUK 5:30 The good thing is that Jesus was thinking and not just blinded by religious dos and don?t. Unfortunately many Christians stopped using their brains when it comes to the issue of faith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 08:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/1/</guid>
      <description>LUK 1:77 To be a teacher and a preacher of God?s means of salvation through forgiveness of sins. I am also commissioned to do the same except with powers and backed by the Holy Spirit as much as John and Jesus. I cannot do this without him
Related verses: Luke 1:77. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 12:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/4/</guid>
      <description>LUK 4:28 God&amp;rsquo;s grace to the gentiles was the major reason why Jesus was rejected in his hometown and thereby they stumbled at the Messiah and could not receive him
Related verses: Luke 4:28. See notes
LUK 4:23 The answer was simple. It was from God. When I learn to look at the right things, I will be blessed and have more understanding.
Jesus was a carpenter and it was only possible to have performed his miracles through God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 19</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 11:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/19/</guid>
      <description>LUK 19:26 God has given me a gift but I have disregarded it. I need to work harder because of the day fo accountability. If I want it to be increased I have to step out in faith and ignore my reputation and what people say about me. In the end I am only working for God and the fear of man will put me in a snare
Related verses: LUKE 19:26.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 14</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 08:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/14/</guid>
      <description>LUK 14:27 You can&amp;rsquo;t love anyone more than yourself naturally that&amp;rsquo;s why Jesus said love your NEIGHBOR AS YOURSELF.
the most important person I need to lose is MYSELF. Ministry is work and God pays for our services.
he has already paid me through the blood of his son Jesus.
 PUT GOD FIRST. GIVE YOUR TIME AND EFFORT  pride is putting yourself first.
Related verses: LUKE 14:26-27. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 11</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 14:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/11/</guid>
      <description>LUK 11:8 Persistence and boldness overrides giving in relationships. We can use persistence and boldness to get things from our father in heaven
Related verses: LUKE 11:8. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 7</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 10:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/7/</guid>
      <description>LUK 7:46 Simon didn&amp;rsquo;t give Jesus the proper treatment of a guest yet he had the guts to critically analyse Jesus and the immoral woman.
The woman heard about Jesus and made her way there with a very expensive perfume and gave Jesus the proper treatment of a guest.
I must not criticise men of God and must give them the proper treatment. The woman left with the joy that her sins had been forgiven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUK 8</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 08:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/luk/8/</guid>
      <description>LUK 8:5 The word of God will be of no use to me if I deem it useless or worthless to change my situation just as the birds of the air came to eat up the seeds after IT HAD BEEN TRODDEN DOWN
Related verses: Luke 8:5. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
