<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ACT on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/act/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ACT on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 09:26:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/act/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ACT 24</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 09:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/24/</guid>
      <description>ACT 24:25 Felix was probably pricked to the heart because he was lacking in these characteristics just like John the Baptist to Herod. Although Felix had an accurate understanding of Christianity
Related verses: Acts 24:25. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 21</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/21/</guid>
      <description>ACT 21:8 Philip the evangelist lived in Caesarea and had 4 virgin daughters who had the gift of prophecy. Which means all five were believers and had the Holy Spirit operating in their lives
Related verses: Acts 21:8-9. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 20</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 09:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/20/</guid>
      <description>ACT 20:24 I will be able to fulfill my ministry if I don&amp;rsquo;t consider my life of any value
Related verses: Acts 20:24. See notes
ACT 20:11 Paul spoke from the previous day past midnight even until daybreak
Related verses: Acts 20:11. See notes
ACT 20:9 Apostle Paul was not stingy with words. A learned man. Gifted in articulation of words and full of power. A great servant of Jesus. A devotee and lover of God who was ready to murder for God until he encountered Jesus on the road to Damascus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 19</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 09:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/19/</guid>
      <description>ACT 19:30 Radical
Related verses: Acts 19:30. See notes
ACT 19:14 Being the son of a high priest guarantees nothing. A personal relationship with Jesus is all that is needed
Related verses: Acts 19:14. See notes
ACT 19:13 They didn&amp;rsquo;t know Jesus personally so the name of Jesus didn&amp;rsquo;t work for them. The name of Jesus us more than just the name. It includes his person, attributes, character and requires a personal relationship with him which comes by revelation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 15</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 09:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/15/</guid>
      <description>ACT 15:32 Judas (Barsabbas) and Silas (Silvanus) were prophets
Related verses: Acts 15:32. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 14</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 09:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/14/</guid>
      <description>ACT 14:23 In choosing leaders of the church for the work of the ministry, there were prayer and fasting involved.
First in Jesus choosing the Apostles, then in the church commissioning Paul and Barnabas then in Paul choosing elders in each church they had preached in e.g. Antioch, Lystra, Derbe
Related verses: Acts 14:23. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 11</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 09:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/11/</guid>
      <description>ACT 11:26 They met in the the church. A physical place
Related verses: Acts 11:26. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 10</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 09:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/10/</guid>
      <description>ACT 10:20 The Holy Spirit sent an angel to Cornelius to send men to Peter and the Holy Spirit spoke to Peter himself.
Could this be because Peter was saved and Cornelius wasn&amp;rsquo;t yet saved. Meaning the Holy Spirit speaks to the believers only.
Related verses: Acts 10:19-20. See notes
ACT 10:8 Cornelius explanation ensured that the work would be carried out effectively.
Related verses: Acts 10:8. See notes
ACT 10:4 Cornelius prayer and offering invoked the mercy of God to see that he and his family received salvation even though he was a Roman officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 9</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 10:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/9/</guid>
      <description>ACT 9:25 Saul had gained disciples in the space of three years
Related verses: Acts 9:25. See notes
ACT 9:17 Saul had become born again and was praying but Ananias had to go to him to lay hands on him not just to receive his sight but to be filled with the Holy Spirit.
When Philip the evangelist preached in Samaria, Apostle Peter and John had to come and lay hands on the people of Samaria to receive the Holy Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 7</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 09:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/7/</guid>
      <description>ACT 7:59 The spirit of man goes to heaven. The soul goes to hell, the body perishes on the earth
Related verses: Ecclesiastes 12:7, Luke 23:46, Acts 7:59. See notes
ACT 7:33 To take off one?s shoe is to show respect and humility. Slaves in old times didn?t wear sandals. Only their masters did and the slaves were required to stoop down to untie the master?s sandals. In so doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 07:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/1/</guid>
      <description>ACT 1:1 I must do before teaching
Related verses: Matthew 23:3, Acts 1:1. See notes
ACT 1:1 Written by Luke to Theophilus. Jesus first began to do, then he taught. Preaching of salvation should first be from Jerusalem then to the rest of the world
Related verses: Acts 1:1. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 12</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 10:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/12/</guid>
      <description>ACT 12:22 Mercy I must be careful to prevent people from worshiping me. when this happens it means I have become very proud to the point of being destroyed.
I must always give the glory to God
Related verses: Acts 12:22-23. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 11:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/5/</guid>
      <description>ACT 5:4 The Holy spirit is God. Lying to him is lying to God and that has grave consequences
Related verses: Acts of the Apostles 5:4. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 03:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/2/</guid>
      <description>ACT 2:33 The Trinity mentioned here. God the Father gave the son the Holy spirit to pour out on me so that I can be like the son.
Related verses: Acts of the Apostles 2:33. See notes
ACT 2:6 The Holy spirit draws people of different nations. He bridges the gap between people.
Pray for the Holy spirit
Related verses: ACTS 2:6. See notes
ACT 2:2 They 120 were probably in the temple and not the upper room as explained from the NASB study Bible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 28</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 10:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/28/</guid>
      <description>ACT 28:8 Healing is not just for sicknesses and diseases caused by demons but all sicknesses including fever and dysentery.
Paul prayed then laid his hands on the sick man.
Related verses: ACTS 28:8. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 16</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 12:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/16/</guid>
      <description>ACT 16:4 The Apostles and the elders of the church gave out the decrees.
Paul, Silas and Timothy simply delivered it for them to observe
Related verses: ACTS 16:4. See notes
ACT 16:14 Lydia was the first recorded convert in Europe. She was already a worshipper of God but needed to be saved by the preaching of the gospel. God opened her heart and she received the gospel of salvation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 13</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 07:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/13/</guid>
      <description>ACT 13:31 Jesus appeared to the people who cane up with him from Galilee to Jerusalem. These were his true disciples.
Only those who were present had the privilege of seeing him after he resurrected and also became witnesses.
Related verses: ACTS 13:31. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACT 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 06:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/act/4/</guid>
      <description>ACT 4:3 Just after they had received the Holy Spirit and Peter had won 3000 souls, a lame man has also been healed and Peter and John had their first recorded prison experience.
It is inevitable to walk in Jesus anointing and not be persecuted. Jesus had warned previously that if they can do that to the master, the disciples should get ready to experience the same.
Related verses: ACTS 4:3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
