<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JAS on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/jas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JAS on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 09:57:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/jas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JAS 3</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jas/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 09:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jas/3/</guid>
      <description>JAS 3:18 The seed of divine wisdom produces the fruit of righteousness and this also brings forth peace
Related verses: Isaiah 32:17, James 3:18. See notes
JAS 3:16 Be strong in the Lord. Not in the gym, or physics, fighting, sports or in PhD. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong. Being strong in education or gym is good but the main aim is to be strong in the Lord and in the power of his might.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JAS 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jas/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 11:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jas/5/</guid>
      <description>JAS 5:7 Waiting on God will make me spiritual. My only agenda is God. I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be planning anything while waiting on God
Related verses: James 5:7. See notes
JAS 5:9 I will be judged if i keep complaining against my brother. The best thing I can do is overlook faults or just keep shut and leave it in God?s hands.
Related verses: JAMES 5:9. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JAS 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jas/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 16:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jas/4/</guid>
      <description>JAS 4:7 I need to submit to God?s word and his authority then resist the devil.
Submission comes before resistance. I must resist evil after I have submitted to God and he will flee from me. My submission to God gives me authority over the devil.
Submission means to place yourself in the control of another.
Just as yielding myself to do evil continually makes the Holy Spirit depart from me so is the same with yielding myself to God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JAS 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jas/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 13:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jas/2/</guid>
      <description>JAS 2:17 Faith produces and requires a visible action to be proven genuine
Related verses: JAMES 2:17. See notes
JAS 2:14 Genuine faith produces good works.
Related verses: JAMES 2:14. See notes
JAS 2:24 It is faith in Jesus that saves us and not works. Valid faith is shown through works that is why every faith must be accompanied by evidence.
&amp;hellip; For faith is the evidence of things not seen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JAS 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jas/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 12:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/jas/1/</guid>
      <description>JAS 1:26 My tongue and the words of my mouth can be used to judge my faith.
I cannot claim to be a Christian and still use curse words.
Related verses: JAMES 1:26. See notes
JAS 1:19 Quick to hear, slow speak.
Paying attention to God&amp;rsquo;s words and being slow to speak so you don&amp;rsquo;t say anything rash.
Even a fool is thought to be wise when he keeps his mouth shut.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
