<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DAN on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/dan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DAN on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 05:22:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/dan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DAN 9</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 05:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/9/</guid>
      <description>DAN 9:2 This is where Daniel got his revelation about when they would be free from exile (70 years)
When there is the shedding of innocent blood and idolatry, judgement is soon to come.
Related verses: Leviticus 26:34, 2 Chronicles 36:21, Jeremiah 25:11, Daniel 9:2. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAN 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 10:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/6/</guid>
      <description>DAN 6:18 This is another type of fast where there is no eating in the evening and music, pleasure and entertainment is disregarded
Related verses: Daniel 6:18. See notes
DAN 6:7 A way to trap Daniel was through the law of his God. God wants us to establish authority and this should only change when the law of our rulers directly conflicts the law of God.
The Medes and the Persians along with the Egyptians also engaged in human worship</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAN 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 12:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/5/</guid>
      <description>DAN 5:27 A throne is established by righteous judgement. Belshazzar was found wanting on the scale of righteousness and judgement has been set. the climax of his unrighteous act was dishonouring God by drinking from the cup of God and praising idols
Related verses: Daniel 5:27. See notes
DAN 5:18 It was God who have King Nebuchadnezzar the kingdom as well as greatness, glory and majesty. this compelled nations to be subjected to him</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAN 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 02:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/4/</guid>
      <description>DAN 4:36 God is so wonderful in the sense that he adds to our glory after we have fallen or been through a time of testing. examples are Job, Joseph, Nebuchadnezzar and Jesus etc.
Related verses: Daniel 4:36. See notes
DAN 4:30 Babylon talks of a city or venture built by the strength and wisdom of men and with which God is not given the honor or glory in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAN 3</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 10:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/3/</guid>
      <description>DAN 3:15 This has been the statement of mighty rulers before their downfall. Senacherrib taunted the God of Israel as well as Nebuchadnezzar before their downfall
Related verses: 2 Chronicles 32:13-17, Daniel 3:15. See notes
DAN 3:18 In the case of the three Hebrew men who refused to bow down to the idol. They were convicted and would rather lose their life than worship an idol.
They boldly went against the order of the king even though the penalty was being roasted to ashes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAN 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 09:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/2/</guid>
      <description>DAN 2:49 Daniel did not forget his friends when he was elevated
Related verses: Daniel 2:49. See notes
DAN 2:17 In the multitude of counsel there is safety. I need like-minded companions
Related verses: Daniel 2:17. See notes
DAN 2:48 The dream revealed what was to come in the future and a Jew became ruler in a foreign land through the revelation of dreams.
Related verses: Daniel 2:48. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAN 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 10:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/dan/1/</guid>
      <description>DAN 1:7 names are used as identity and they have meaning. they reveal the character and attributes of a person.
The four men&amp;rsquo;s names were changed to affect their desire for the true God. Israel wanted to serve idols and God gave them their desires and took them to a land where they could serve a lot of gods.
Everything in Babylon was set up to change the culture and mindset of the Israelites but Daniel, Azariah, Mishael and Hananiah were different.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
