<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1KI on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/1ki/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1KI on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 01:27:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/1ki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1KI 10</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 01:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/10/</guid>
      <description>1KI 10:2 Prophecy to what finally happened when Jesus was born. Wise men from the east brought Gold, Frankincense and myrrh
Related verses: 1 Kings 10:2, Isaiah 60:6, Matthew 2:1. See notes
1KI 10:10 Gold, frankincense and myrrh were gifts given to kings. it was worthy of Jesus to receive those gifts because he was the king of kings
Related verses: 1 Kings 10:10, Matthew 2:11. See notes
1KI 10:28 Kue, known as Cilicia in new testament times was the home province of Apostle Paul</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 3</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 08:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/3/</guid>
      <description>1KI 3:28 The word of God as the sword of the spirit dividing the soul and the spirit to reveal the thoughts and intentions of the heart
Related verses: 1 Kings 3:24, 1 Kings 3:27-28, Luke 2:35, Hebrews 4:12. See notes
1KI 3:28 The wisdom of God is important in administering justice as was given to Solomon
Related verses: 1 Kings 3:28. See notes
1KI 3:28 The wisdom of God would make people reverence you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 17</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 10:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/17/</guid>
      <description>1KI 17:12 When all hope was lost in a corrupt land, God sent an Elijah to a widow in an unbelieving city
Related verses: 1 Kings 17:12. See notes
1KI 17:19 When the woman surrendered the dead boy to the man of God, God resurrected him and brought him back to the woman.
The boy was taken to the upper room before he got resurrected after which he was taken back down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 14</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 15:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/14/</guid>
      <description>1KI 14:24 these male cult orodtitutes engaged in homosexual acts. this was the lot of Sodom and Gomorrah before they were destroyed
Related verses: 1 Kings 14:24. See notes
1KI 14:9 God was provoked to anger because of idolatry and considered it evil
Related verses: 1 Kings 14:9. See notes
1KI 14:26 After all the labour that Solomon had subjected men to in acquiring all these good works, all was vanity as Shishak the brother-in-law of Jeroboam ransacked the temple in Jerusalem and took away all the shields of gold</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 13</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 08:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/13/</guid>
      <description>1KI 13:18 the prophet lied to the man of God than an angel had appeared to him to I form the man if God to go back and eat (thus contradicting the instructions that God gave the man of God).
no angel or man should be able to make me disobey the clear words given to me by God.
this was the same error that Adam and Eve committed after God has given a clear instruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 12</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 10:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/12/</guid>
      <description>1KI 12:7 Leadership starts with humility and servanthood. Rehoboam listened to the wrong advice and lost most of the kingdom.
The people weren&amp;rsquo;t interested in being completely free. All they asked for was the burden to be lighter but Rehoboam in his foolishness lost the people&amp;rsquo;s support by being unreasonable
Related verses: 1 Kings 12:7. See notes
1KI 12:27 Doubt can rob us of God&amp;rsquo;s promises. Even though God had elevated Jeroboam and have made him king of Israel and made a covenant to obey God, he decided to make the Israelites serve calves as they did before in the wilderness after they went away from Egypt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/4/</guid>
      <description>1KI 4:15 The name sounds Egyptian. she&amp;rsquo;s probably the daughter of the Egyptian woman he married.
Basemath doesn&amp;rsquo;t sound like an Israeli name. it may be possible, another daughter of Solomon&amp;rsquo;s foreign wives
Related verses: 1 Kings 4:11, 1 Kings 4:15. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 9</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/9/</guid>
      <description>1KI 9:15 Solomon a wise man was always involved in building projects. He built structures for 20 years. He built the temple, his house, house of Pharaoh&amp;rsquo;s daughter, he even built fortifications and ships.
Related verses: 1 Kings 9:15, 1 Kings 9:17, 1 Kings 9:19, 1 Kings 9:24-25. See notes
1KI 9:5 throne established forever on condition of obedience to God
Related verses: 1 Kings 9:5. See notes
1KI 9:2 The second time God appeared to Solomon to confirm that he had answered his prayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 8</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 06:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/8/</guid>
      <description>1KI 8:63 wooow that was a lot of sacrifices. Sacrifices release power no wonder the priests could not even enter the temple to minister because of the intense presence of God (the cloud)
Related verses: 1 Kings 8:63. See notes
1KI 8:54 One of the postures of prayer is to kneel down with hands stretched to heaven. Another is standing, sitting or lying down. I believe that this is the basis for which Muslims do their prayer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 7</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 08:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/7/</guid>
      <description>1KI 7:14 Hiram was filled with the spirit of wisdom, understanding and skill so he was eligible to build the temple of God. It is worth noting that the writer of Chronicles found it worthy to mention that he had a maternal connection with the Israelites
Related verses: 1 Kings 7:14. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 08:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/6/</guid>
      <description>1KI 6:38 The temple was built in 7 years. Solomon was around 31 years at this time. 7 years (a sign of completeness)
Related verses: 1 Kings 6:38. See notes
1KI 6:12 Continuing dynasty on obedience
Related verses: 1 Kings 6:12. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 01:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/5/</guid>
      <description>1KI 5:5 immediate commencement of building the temple of God. Solomon orchestrated the building of the temple at a very young age
Related verses: 1 Kings 5:5. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/2/</guid>
      <description>1KI 2:35 A change in organisation and execution of those who committed treason in the past reign of David brought peace to the reign of Solomon. Solomon merely obeyed his father
Related verses: 1 Kings 2:35. See notes
1KI 2:32 The horns of the altar is of no use protecting a criminal when he has been found out as guilty.
Related verses: 1 Kings 2:32. See notes
1KI 2:27 Gods prophecy to Eli came to total fulfilment after he dismissed Abiathar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 08:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/1/</guid>
      <description>1KI 1:35 Riding on the King&amp;rsquo;s mule, siting on the King&amp;rsquo;s throne and having sex with the King&amp;rsquo;s concubine is a sign of taking over from the King
Related verses: 1 Kings 1:35. See notes
1KI 1:28 It looks like when Nathan the prophet came in, Bathsheba went out as a sign of respect
Related verses: 1 Kings 1:28. See notes
1KI 1:5 David must be handsome for two of his sons to be mentioned as handsome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 22</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 08:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/22/</guid>
      <description>1KI 22:14 Will you speak to please the people or will you speak what God has told you even though it&amp;rsquo;s bad news and 400 prophets are saying otherwise?
Related verses: 1 KINGS 22:13-14. See notes
1KI 22:5 It is always wise to involve God first in your decisions. He knows the best and helped king David a lot of times because David enquirer of him
Related verses: 1 KINGS 22:5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 21</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 08:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/21/</guid>
      <description>1KI 21:20 Ahab regards Elijah the prophet of God as his enemy because Ahab has sold himself to do evil. Inspite of God&amp;rsquo;s mercy on Ahab, he still did not repent. Ahab does have a heart but his wife&amp;rsquo;s continual influence on him made him the monster of a king
Related verses: 1 KINGS 21:20. See notes
1KI 21:25 Repentance averts God&amp;rsquo;s judgement even when it had been spoken. Although it may affect future generations until they decide to avert the judgement completely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 20</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 07:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/20/</guid>
      <description>1KI 20:39 The prophet represented Ahab, the man to be guarded was Ben-Hadad and the man who brought the man to be guarded was God.
God had delivered Ben-Hadad into the hands of Ahab to be devoted for destruction but Ahab made a pact with him and let him escape and Ahab unknowingly pronounced judgement on himself just as David had done when God also sent a prophet to him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 18</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 06:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/18/</guid>
      <description>1KI 18:17 Ahah accusing Elijah of bringing disaster on Israel whereas the truth is Arab is a covenant breaker and has married a high-rank witch who has led Israel into idolatry.
Most times, the guilty are so blinded by their sin that they blame the innocents for their own problems and sins.
Rejecting the commandments of God will bring disaster especially if you are breaking his covenant.
Related verses: 1 KINGS 18:17-18.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1KI 11</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 16:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ki/11/</guid>
      <description>1KI 11:33 Solomon lost the kingdom because
 he abandoned God and served other gods. he disobeyed the ordinances and commandments of God  Related verses: 1 KINGS 11:33. See notes
1KI 11:12 God&amp;rsquo;s faithfulness and mercy is everlasting. Irrespective of the sins of Solomon, God still had mercy and would not completely remove the kingdom of David because of his covenant with David and because of Israel his chosen people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
