<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JOB on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/job/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JOB on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 05:21:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/job/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JOB 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 05:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/2/</guid>
      <description>JOB 2:7 The threshing wheel separates the chaff from the wheat by subjecting the grain to pressure when it is treaded on by both the wheels and the cow threshing the grain.
Satan petitioned God to have Job sifted like wheat but Job&amp;rsquo;s faith did not fail. Satan demanded that Peter would be tested as well but his faith did not fail even when he denied Jesus and went back to fishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/1/</guid>
      <description>JOB 1:1 If I want to depart from evil, I must reverence God and this is God&amp;rsquo;s wisdom and greatness in God&amp;rsquo;s sight. An example is Job who feared God and shunned evil and was described as the greatest of the men of the east.
Related verses: Job 1:1, Job 28:28, Proverbs 16:6. See notes
JOB 1:1 the reason is because Solomon&amp;rsquo;s wisdom was not of this world. it was God&amp;rsquo;s wisdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 28</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/28/</guid>
      <description>JOB 28:28 If I want to depart from evil, I must reverence God and this is God&amp;rsquo;s wisdom and greatness in God&amp;rsquo;s sight. An example is Job who feared God and shunned evil and was described as the greatest of the men of the east.
Related verses: Job 1:1, Job 28:28, Proverbs 16:6. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 20</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 11:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/20/</guid>
      <description>JOB 20:25 the same fate of the wicked. Adultery is also categorised as wickedness
Related verses: Job 20:24-25, Proverbs 7:23. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 42</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/42/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 07:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/42/</guid>
      <description>JOB 42:12 Job was the greatest of all the men in the East yet God blessed him even more by doubling it
Related verses: Job 42:12. See notes
JOB 42:8 Job&amp;rsquo;s friend Eliphaz wasn&amp;rsquo;t present when God spoke to Job. I believe none of Job&amp;rsquo;s other friends were around because God told Eliphaz to go to Job with 7 bulls and 7 rams so he could act as priest on their behalf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 36</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/36/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 06:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/36/</guid>
      <description>JOB 36:14 Some of the cult prostitutes were homosexuals. it was seen as a fertility rite and oh my goodness, what a terrible atrocity.
I believe this is the same practice in Sodom, Gomorrah, Admah and Zeboim.
I believe they indulged in idol worship which permitted them to indulge in homosexuality and that became the culture of the city.
unfortunately this is where all false religion ends up people in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 31</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 06:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/31/</guid>
      <description>JOB 31:15 Everyone deserves to be treated equally, the God I serve made us both
Related verses: Job 31:15. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 23</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 05:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/23/</guid>
      <description>JOB 23:10 Job is confident he hadn&amp;rsquo;t done anything to deserve anything he was facing due to the understanding of his time that blessings is directly proportional to godliness (which is actually true in the long run).
Job is now experienced to know that in the short run that isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily always true yet his friends accuse him of wickedness.
Job thinks when God has tried him, he will be found innocent of the punishment he&amp;rsquo;s facing due to his sin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 22</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 05:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/22/</guid>
      <description>JOB 22:30 lol it&amp;rsquo;s actually funny that this was exactly what happened to Eliphaz. God told Job to pray for his three friends after they had misrepresented God and said false statements about Job&amp;rsquo;s integrity
Related verses: Job 22:30. See notes
JOB 22:5 False accusations. we can&amp;rsquo;t judge by circumstances the Integrity of a person.
in ancient times blessings is directly associated with righteous and the devil tries to break this bond by imploring God to do that in the life of Job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 29</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 02:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/29/</guid>
      <description>JOB 29:12 Cooperating with God. Helping the helpless (widows, orphans, strangers)
Related verses: JOB 29:12-13. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 27</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 07:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/27/</guid>
      <description>JOB 27:6 What a man. There would be many questions running in Job&amp;rsquo;s minds coupled with his friend&amp;rsquo;s accusations, he still held fast to his integrity
Related verses: JOB 27:6. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 19</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 06:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/19/</guid>
      <description>JOB 19:13 Many people deserted Job in his affliction. It is easy to say you suffered this because you have sinned but that&amp;rsquo;s not always true. Job is so confident that he hasn&amp;rsquo;t done anything wrong that he is willing to go to court with God but needs a lawyer. But what lawyer can even stand before the almighty God.
Job accused God of doing evil to him. Although God didn&amp;rsquo;t do any of these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 07:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/5/</guid>
      <description>JOB 5:17 If God reproves you, it means you have a good relationship with him. Like a father does to his own dear son
Related verses: JOB 5:17. See notes
JOB 5:12 You cannot enjoy the work of your hands if you attained them using evil schemes
Related verses: JOB 5:12. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOB 3</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 07:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/job/3/</guid>
      <description>JOB 3:25 Job always sacrificed animals for his children because he thought they might have cursed God in their heart but unfortunately, they died anyway.
One thing to notice is that Satan is trying to break the link between righteousness and blessings, so that he would expose the righteous man for the sinner he is (by cursing God) - NASB study Bible
It is also great to know that God himself didn&amp;rsquo;t kill any of Job&amp;rsquo;s children nor did he inflict him with sores or ruin his business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
