<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1CH on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/1ch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1CH on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 10:17:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/1ch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1CH 29</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 10:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/29/</guid>
      <description>1CH 29:23 The throne Solomon sat on was God&amp;rsquo;s throne. he was just an earthly representative of the heavenly King. He prospered a d was obeyed by his subjects
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 29:23. See notes
1CH 29:19 I need a perfect heart to keep God&amp;rsquo;s commandments but I can also ask God for a perfect heart
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 29:19. See notes
1CH 29:3 David gave from his personal treasure (his money) because he delighted in the house of his God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 28</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 06:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/28/</guid>
      <description>1CH 28:10 Encouragement like Moses and God gave to Joshua. I need to be courageous and brave to build the hose of God. I should not let doubt, dear and intimidation prevent me from doing it
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 28:10. See notes
1CH 28:7 The continuation of establishment is dependent upon my continuity in obeying the word of God
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 28:7. See notes
1CH 28:6 What a privilege to be chosen by God as his son.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 27</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 07:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/27/</guid>
      <description>1CH 27:34 Two people had to replace Ahithophel to match his wisdom. I can be replaced anytime so I need to be humble.
the Bible said he had wisdom such that when he spoke, it was as though someone had heard from God. his divine wisdom was corrupted by unforgiveness and revenge and cost him his life
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 27:34. See notes
1CH 27:32 A man of understanding and wisdom</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 26</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 07:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/26/</guid>
      <description>1CH 26:27 All these were dedicated to make sure the house of God was looking good
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 26:27-28. See notes
1CH 26:24 Grandson of Moses was alive in the time of David. that means that the time between the birth of Gershom and David being King was within 150 to 200 years
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 26:24. See notes
1CH 26:14 Not to be confused with the Zechariah the father of John.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 25</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 04:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/25/</guid>
      <description>1CH 25:5 Heman was a blessed man. For the scriptures to also specifically mention it means there was something about Heman. Apart from Samuel, Gad, Nathan, he was also a seer/prophet.
He was the grandson of Samuel the prophet and son of Joel
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 25:5. See notes
1CH 25:2 the king controlled when Asaph was to begin prophesying and Asaph controlled those under him. there was unity</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 22</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 08:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/22/</guid>
      <description>1CH 22:19 A command to set the heart and mind to seek God and choose him over other things
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 22:19. See notes
1CH 22:13 Similar words of encouragement that God gave Joshua after the death of Moses
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 22:13. See notes
1CH 22:12 Solomon prayed and requested for wisdom and understanding according to the prayers of his father David. It was meant to help him keep the law of God and then peace will manifest</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 21</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 08:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/21/</guid>
      <description>1CH 21:29 But Solomon went there to sacrifice to God finally and built the temple of God. It was here that Solomon received divine wisdom
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 21:29-30. See notes
1CH 21:27 In the spiritual realm, angels can also draw sword and sheath. Most things we have on earth probably already exist in the spirit realm
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 21:27. See notes
1CH 21:20 Ornan and his four sons also saw the angel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 20</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 12:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/20/</guid>
      <description>1CH 20:4 After David killed Goliath, he still fought against 4 other descendants of the Giant. three of their names mentioned: Lahmi (brother of Goliath), Ishbi-Benob, Saph (Sippai)
Related verses: 2 Samuel 21:16, 2 Samuel 21:18-22, 1 Chronicles 20:4-6, 1 Chronicles 20:8. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 19</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 17:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/19/</guid>
      <description>1CH 19:13 Encouragement to fight for God and the people and God gave the victory. I must always trust in God
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 19:13. See notes
1CH 19:4 For lack of good advice, a war started. David had good intentions but evil advice on the part of the counsellor of Hanun the King and his actions led to loss of people&amp;rsquo;s lives.
Cutting of the beard was a sign of mourning as well as ripping of the garment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 05:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/6/</guid>
      <description>1CH 6:32 the priest ministered to God with singing
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 6:32. See notes
1CH 6:8 Zadok was 10th generation from Aaron
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 6:8. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 17</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 08:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/17/</guid>
      <description>1CH 17:27 God&amp;rsquo;s blessings last forever and adds no sorrow
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 17:27. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 16</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 05:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/16/</guid>
      <description>1CH 16:10 there is joy in seeking the Lord
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 16:10. See notes
1CH 16:27 Being in the presence of God guarantees me splendor, majesty, strength and joy
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 16:27. See notes
1CH 16:7 this is the Asaph that is mentioned in some of the Psalms. here David appoints him and gives him the primary role of giving thanks to God
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 16:7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 15</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 03:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/15/</guid>
      <description>1CH 15:22 Skill is important in worshipping God but he wasn&amp;rsquo;t just a skilled singer, he was also a Levite chosen of God in the things concerning ministering the things of God.
Levites were in charge of the Holy things and in carrying the ark but according to their division
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 15:22. See notes
1CH 15:2 After the right measures were taken, no death occurred in transporting the ark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 14</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 07:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/14/</guid>
      <description>1CH 14:2 only for the sake of God&amp;rsquo;s people
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 14:2. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 12</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/12/</guid>
      <description>1CH 12:40 There was joy in Israel at the ordination of David as king over Israel. people prepared food and brought it over and the people were in unity
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 12:40. See notes
1CH 12:12 David had gain valuable leadership experience in the house of Saul. His life was now in danger and he had been put in charge of another (approximately 400) men. At least we know that David&amp;rsquo;s brothers (Eliab, Abinadab, Shammah, Nethanel, Raddai and Orem) came to meet him as well as or most likely (Joab, Abishai and Asahel)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 10</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 09:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/10/</guid>
      <description>1CH 10:14 From this verse, I have learnt that I must consult God on every circumstance and I must be obedient to God&amp;rsquo;s word. Only God deserves my attention and I must seek help from him.
God owns his ministry and it&amp;rsquo;s his will I must seek otherwise God will replace me
Related verses: 1 Chronicles 10:13-14. See notes
1CH 10:10 The temple of Dagon was located at Beth-shan. The Philistines worshipped female diety goddesses as well as Dagon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 13</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 01:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/13/</guid>
      <description>1CH 13:10 God had commanded in Exodus 25:12-15 that the ark should be carried on poles through the four rings. The instruction was followed by the Israelites during the times of Moses and Aaron up until the Philistines captured it.
The Philistines did send it back on cows because they didn?t know better but they at least showed respect and God honoured it by allowing their guess [if the oxen went towards the land of Israel] to come to pass to show that it was him (God) who struck the Philistines with tumours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 11</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 00:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/11/</guid>
      <description>1CH 11:9 David became greater and GREATER because the Lord. The Lord of all armies was with him.
Who can stand against the Lord of Host. Not even the devil or any witch, wizard, demon or occultist power can withstand such mighty force from the Lord.
Related verses: 1 CHRONICLES 11:9. See notes
1CH 11:6 This is the secret to Joab being made chief and commander. Took the first step being bold and fearless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 7</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 11:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/7/</guid>
      <description>1CH 7:24 Even though Beriah?s name means (on misfortune), he bore a daughter who made a good name. We?ve always read about men building cities but this lady whose name was Sheerah made a name for herself.
The fact that you had a past shouldn?t determine your future. She could have decided that since my father?s name means misfortune, then I would continue to live unfortunate by doing nothing. But no, that didn?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1CH 3</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 14:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1ch/3/</guid>
      <description>1CH 3:2 David had at least 20 recorded children of which 1 was a lady. Tamar by name (sister to Absalom)
Related verses: 1 CHRONICLES 3:1-9. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
