<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EXO on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/exo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in EXO on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 09:42:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/exo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EXO 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 09:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/5/</guid>
      <description>EXO 5:1 Jesus fed them until they were satisfied. Everyone ate and the disciples had full baskets left for themselves.
When we follow Jesus he provides for our needs. He is our great shepherd so we will not lack any good thing.
Related verses: Exodus 5:1, Psalms 23:1, Mark 6:42. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 16</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 07:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/16/</guid>
      <description>EXO 16:33 The manna ceased but the law lasted forever. Man cannot live forever by eating bread or manna but man will have everlasting life if he abides by the word of God.
both manna and the commandments were given by God yet one was more important than the other.
The commandments lasted generations but the manna didn&amp;rsquo;t even though both were provided by God. it goes to show that the spiritual is greater than the natural.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 22</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 16:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/22/</guid>
      <description>EXO 22:28 He cursed the king and the punishment that David saw fit was death. I must be careful not to curse God or even the leader he has placed above me even in my thoughts because nothing is secret in this world. it&amp;rsquo;s only a matter of time
Related verses: Exodus 22:28, 2 Samuel 16:5, 1 Kings 2:9, Ecclesiastes 10:20. See notes
EXO 22:2 It then is better not to be a thief at all because what&amp;rsquo;s the point of stealing and being killed at night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 40</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/40/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 06:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/40/</guid>
      <description>EXO 40:38 The cloud and the fire were visible manifestations of the presence of God.
They waited when God&amp;rsquo;s presence was present and moved only when God&amp;rsquo;s presence also moved. God was leading his people. The Holy spirit symbolises the cloud and the fire.
Related verses: Exodus 40:38. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 39</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/39/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 06:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/39/</guid>
      <description>EXO 39:43 When I do things according to the way God wants it, I provoke a blessing.
Related verses: Exodus 39:43. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 36</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/36/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 07:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/36/</guid>
      <description>EXO 36:5 When God stirs my heart, I will provide abundantly or do more than required in the things I do for God
Related verses: Exodus 36:5. See notes
EXO 36:1 It is God that gives the ability and the skill to do some things especially pertaining to the ministry
Related verses: Exodus 36:1. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 35</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/35/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 07:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/35/</guid>
      <description>EXO 35:34 Anointing to teach. Anointing enhances your skill, wisdom and understanding
Related verses: Exodus 35:34. See notes
EXO 35:10 intelligent people are also needed for the work of the ministry
Related verses: Exodus 35:10. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 34</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/34/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 14:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/34/</guid>
      <description>EXO 34:29 The reason his skin glowed was because he had been with God for forty days and forty night. The presence of God had permeated him so much that he became a different person.
That was the glory of God. the same happened when Peter, James and John saw Jesus glory on the mount of transfiguration when his face and cloth shone brighter than the sun
Related verses: Exodus 34:29.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 32</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/32/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 08:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/32/</guid>
      <description>EXO 32:11 Moses understood the heart of God. I don&amp;rsquo;t think God really wanted to destroy them. that would have been the last resort because my God is full of mercy and compassion.
Moses reversed the word. Whereas God had initially said to Moses, YOUR PEOPLE, Moses now interceded telling God that this is YOUR PEOPLE whom you brought out of Egypt
Related verses: Exodus 32:11. See notes
EXO 32:7 God disowned Israel lol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 30</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 09:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/30/</guid>
      <description>EXO 30:32 The Holy anointing oil is sacred and must neither be poured on a layman nor made in the same composition because the anointing oil is sacred and represents the Holy spirit. there is nothing else in comparison with the Holy Spirit.
It must only be poured in those chosen to be anointed by God
Related verses: Exodus 30:32-33. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 28</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 07:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/28/</guid>
      <description>EXO 28:5 The garments was there to enable them to serve as priests. Also the garment was for beautification and honour amongst other people.
This so what God intents for those who serve as priests. Who teaches and intercedes on behalf of the people
Related verses: Exodus 28:4-5. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 17</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 23:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/17/</guid>
      <description>EXO 17:11 Moses raising up his hands was a sign of appeal to God for help and enablement (NASB study Bible). The outcome of the battle was spiritually decided. If Amalek knew this, they would just focus on killing Moses rather than fighting any battle.
As long as Moses hands were lifted up, the battle was won. As long as my hands are lifted up to God for help, he will help and save me because my hands is short and can become fatigued but his hands is not short that it cannot save neither can God be fatigued</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 20</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 12:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/20/</guid>
      <description>EXO 20:7 Using the name of God in vain is to perform any act or sat any thing that tarnishes, diminishes or Dishonored the characters and attributes of God
Related verses: Exodus 20:7. See notes
EXO 20:6 The proof that I love Jesus is obeying is commandments. The effect of that is his presence because Jesus said he and his father will come to live with me.
I already have the Holy spirit living in me but for Jesus and God to come as well that&amp;rsquo;s another level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 19</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 12:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/19/</guid>
      <description>EXO 19:24 Absolute obedience without regards for personal comfort is a trait of humility
Related verses: Exodus 19:24. See notes
EXO 19:21 Only Moses was permitted to see God. Anyone who tried to see God will be put to death immediately
Related verses: Exodus 19:21. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 18</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 12:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/18/</guid>
      <description>EXO 18:21 Moses obeyed the voice and advise of his father in-law. he wasn&amp;rsquo;t proud to say who are you? He wasn&amp;rsquo;t arrogant to say look I rescued the people out of Egypt. He listened to the advice which wa probably from God through Jethro his father in-law.
the requirements of the people to be chosen as leaders were
 competent men reverently fears God truthful hate dishonest gains  Related verses: Exodus 18:21, Exodus 18:24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 8</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 07:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/8/</guid>
      <description>EXO 8:22 Omnipresent God
Related verses: Exodus 8:22. See notes
EXO 8:18 This book shows that the occult, magic arts and witchcraft is real. The devil can mimic God?s power but no one has the ability to create life except Yahweh.
The sorcerers were able to turn a staff to a snake, water into blood and bring out frogs from the river Nile but were unable to create gnats from the dust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 3</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 11:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/3/</guid>
      <description>EXO 3:21 God&amp;rsquo;s favour ensures that I don&amp;rsquo;t go empty handed
Related verses: Exodus 3:21. See notes
EXO 3:18 God even told Moses to say please when addressing Pharaoh. so what excuses do we have not to be decent and of good manners
Related verses: Exodus 3:18. See notes
EXO 3:21 God said he will make sure his people who didn&amp;rsquo;t come empty handed would not leave empty-handed.
God gave them divine favour such that they will plunder the Egyptians even without war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 10:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/2/</guid>
      <description>EXO 2:9 She got paid to nurse her own child. Just as Noah&amp;rsquo;s ark was covered in tar and pitch to prevent water penetration and it acted as a sign of salvation, so was Moses, the Hebrew saviour who is a type of Jesus our saviour
Related verses: Exodus 2:9. See notes
EXO 2:9 Moses mum got paid for nursing her own son. God has a way of making a bad thing good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 13:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/1/</guid>
      <description>EXO 1:21 By wisdom, a house is built and by understanding it is established. The midwives feared God (beginning of wisdom) and God established a house for them.
Related verses: Exodus 1:21. See notes
EXO 1:17 The two Hebrew midwives feared God and didn&amp;rsquo;t commit murder. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to do the will of your boss if it goes against God&amp;rsquo;s will.
If the Hebrew midwives had terminated Moses, Joshua or Caleb&amp;rsquo;s life, Israel would have rotted in Egypt without a deliverer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 13:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/4/</guid>
      <description>EXO 4:4 God was sending Moses to the Israelites but not without signs and wonders. He empowered Moses to do the undoable.
Moses ran away from the staff turned snake but God told him to take the snake by the tail. &amp;lsquo;Who does that&amp;rsquo;. God was directly telling him to confront his fears. God was saying &amp;lsquo;i make the harmless deadly and the deadly harmless.
Second empowerment was turning a healthy hand to a diseased one and a diseased one to a healthy flesh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 25</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 20:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/25/</guid>
      <description>EXO 25:9 God was specific about the design. God is always specific in his word and that&amp;rsquo;s why we are to fully obey him by paying attention to his word. Partial obedience is still disobedience.
Related verses: Sh&amp;rsquo;mot (Exo) 25:9. See notes
EXO 25:8 THEY will make for GOD a sanctuary where he will dwell. Just as we are to offer our body a living sacrifice and it is a temple of the Holy Ghost but it needs to be according to God&amp;rsquo;s word and specification</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 24</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 00:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/24/</guid>
      <description>EXO 24:12 God gave Moses the task to teach what has been written by God.
In the New Testament, we would deem him a great Apostle :), Prophet, Evangelist, Pastor and Teacher.
Moses was a Priest and Prophet. He operated in 6 different offices
Related verses: Sh&amp;rsquo;mot (Exo) 24:12. See notes
EXO 24:1 The 70 elders of Israel were the 70 descendants of Jacob who came with him or was already in Egypt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 23</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 10:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/23/</guid>
      <description>EXO 23:29 God is also considerate of nature irrespective of his spiritual capabilities. Strategic planning is involved here as driving out the Canaanites, Hittites, Jebusites, Hivites, Amorites etc would cause the multiplication of wild animals.
These group of people are also needed to play their role so that the Israelites would in turn enjoy the fruit of their (not Israeli&amp;rsquo;s) labour.
Related verses: Sh&amp;rsquo;mot (Exo) 23:29. See notes
EXO 23:25 He and I signifying there are two entities involved in this speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXO 13</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 13:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/exo/13/</guid>
      <description>EXO 13:17 God would not take the Israelites through shortcuts because they were not able to prove their preparation for warfare otherwise they would return back to Egypt, the land of son and bondage. Instead he take them through roundabouts, even though it was long, it was to prepare them carefully for the future and the promises ahead.
They had to be trained and tested so that they can be purified and fit for the promise land</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
