<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MRK on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/mrk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MRK on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 10:11:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/mrk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MRK 9</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 10:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/9/</guid>
      <description>MRK 9:7 The testimony of the father was confirmed in the Jordan River where Jacob wrestled with an angel after he crossed it and received a blessing.
The Jordan was also where Jesus received the anointing after being baptized. The Jordan was also where Elisha had received the double portion of the anointing when they divided it and crossed on foot.
The father also testified on the mountain. John the Baptist the first witness, the three disciples (Peter, James and John), the second witness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 8</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 09:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/8/</guid>
      <description>MRK 8:26 The man whose sight was restored was not from the village in Bethsaida. Unbelief was high in Bethsaida and Jesus denounced the city for their unbelief
Related verses: Mark 8:26. See notes
MRK 8:37 The life of man is too costly that the penalty was death. Only God is the author of life and only he has the right to take it.
Related verses: Psalms 49:8, Mark 8:35-37. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 09:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/6/</guid>
      <description>MRK 6:42 Jesus fed them until they were satisfied. Everyone ate and the disciples had full baskets left for themselves.
When we follow Jesus he provides for our needs. He is our great shepherd so we will not lack any good thing.
Related verses: Exodus 5:1, Psalms 23:1, Mark 6:42. See notes
MRK 6:31 Jesus fed the people and also ensured that the disciples also had food to eat.
Man shall not live by bread ALONE but man still needs blood</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 10:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/5/</guid>
      <description>MRK 5:18 Jesus did not let the gentle man to be his disciple because Jesus only came for the Jews.
And the Holy Spirit was to be poured out on Jews first before the gentiles
Related verses: Mark 5:18. See notes
MRK 5:20 None of Jesus disciples were gentiles. The demoniac wanted to join Jesus but Jesus forbid him and instead commissioned him to preach in the 10 gentile cities of Decapolis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 10:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/1/</guid>
      <description>MRK 1:4 A change of thinking patterns which then affects the actions
Related verses: Mark 1:4. See notes
MRK 1:22 The God-given authority to teach came after he had been baptized in water and by the Holy Spirit.
Related verses: Mark 1:22. See notes
MRK 1:4 Baptism was an outward sign of repentance of sin and turning to God to be forgiven
Related verses: Mark 1:4. See notes
MRK 1:3 God is calling Jesus Lord here showing that Jesus has a higher status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 10</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 05:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/10/</guid>
      <description>MRK 10:45 Jesus main purpose was to be a servant of humanity freeing us from the penalty of sin, removing our guilt and covering our shame.
he gave his life as an exchange for us
Related verses: Mark 10:45. See notes
MRK 10:43 Eradicates selfish ambition A big responsibility for being first. I can&amp;rsquo;t expect anything in return.
Serve others and give your life for them
Related verses: Mark 10:43-45. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 15</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 06:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/15/</guid>
      <description>MRK 15:38 On the sabbath there was no buying and selling and work so Jesus had to die earlier otherwise his body would not be buried and although the death of the crucified usually lasted about 2 to 3 days, Jesus died just six hours after being crucified because he willingly released his spirit. Because there was only three hours left, Jesus was buried before the sabbath started.
There was no time to embalm him and Jews didn?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 14</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 07:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/14/</guid>
      <description>MRK 14:16 When I obey my leader, I will find it as he has said. It makes my life easy
Related verses: Mark 14:16. See notes
MRK 14:8 Either Mary Magdalene knew what she was doing or was moved by the Holy Spirit to do it but Jesus knew it was something that needed to be done.
She spent almost a year worth of wages to purchase the perfume. That probably was her savings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 13</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 09:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/13/</guid>
      <description>MRK 13:11 We need not to worry. The Holy Spirit will takeover
Related verses: Mark 13:11. See notes
MRK 13:22 After reading the book &amp;ldquo;Church Mafia&amp;rdquo;, it really enlightened me about how people can deceive others who are not grounded in the scriptures.
Related verses: Mark 13:22. See notes
MRK 13:22 After reading the book &amp;ldquo;Church Mafia&amp;rdquo;, it really enlightened me about how people can deceive others who are not grounded in the scriptures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 12</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 08:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/12/</guid>
      <description>MRK 12:6 The vineyard owner really cared about the fruits that he was willing to risk the lives of so many people. He gave all of them including his son
Related verses: Mark 12:6. See notes
MRK 12:6 The vineyard owner really cared about the fruits that he was willing to risk the lives of so many people. He gave all of them including his son
Related verses: Mark 12:6. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 11</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 22:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/11/</guid>
      <description>MRK 11:13 To do. Take things serious
Related verses: Mark 11:13-14. See notes
MRK 11:13 To do. Take things serious
Related verses: Mark 11:13-14. See notes
MRK 11:13 Having a false representation of things
Related verses: Mark 11:13-14. See notes
MRK 11:13 Having a false representation of things
Related verses: Mark 11:13-14. See notes
MRK 11:24  First forgive those you hold a grudge against, then ask for forgiveness then pray for what you want then speak it to existence by faith without doubting  Related verses: Mark 11:23-25.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 7</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 08:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/7/</guid>
      <description>MRK 7:7 The scriptures carry more weight and references than any tradition that could ever be. Unfortunately, one problem plaguing Christianity is giving it man-made traditions equal value to the scriptures or even more value. This can be seen in a lot of Christian sects. This nullify the word of God and renders it less-effective
Related verses: Mark 7:7. See notes
MRK 7:20 The progression from Genesis 2 where God created man and animals and instructed them to eat plants until their fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 09:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/mrk/4/</guid>
      <description>MRK 4:34 It is a privilege to be a disciple of Jesus because just as the disciples got the chance to hear the deep meaning of Jesus parables, we also have the Holy Spirit too teach and explain things to us that has hidden meanings in the Bible
Related verses: Mark 4:34. See notes
MRK 4:40 I need to have confidence in Jesus. This is when my fears will be taken away</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
