<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1SA on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/1sa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1SA on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 11:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/1sa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1SA 2</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 11:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/2/</guid>
      <description>1SA 2:9 By the arm of flesh shall no man prevail. Assyrian was conquering nations and as small nations were taking cover for protection in Egypt under Pharaoh Shabako, Israel was also tempted to do the same and God was warning them but they didn&amp;rsquo;t listen and neither did they want to repent of idolatry.
Related verses: 1 Samuel 2:9, Isaiah 31:1, Jeremiah 17:5. See notes
1SA 2:32 God cursed his household.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 30</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 08:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/30/</guid>
      <description>1SA 30:31 David and his men were accustomed to go to visit Elders in different places in Judah even during his exile
Related verses: 1 Samuel 30:31. See notes
1SA 30:26 David had elders as friends and sent gifts to them. He walked among old men who were elders of Judah and were responsible for making judgements in the city gates.
He that walks with the wise will also be wise</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 29</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 08:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/29/</guid>
      <description>1SA 29:11 God rescued David from a dilemma. whether he fought against Israel or against the Philistines would have been unhelpful. I believe he would have turned against the Philistines but nevertheless, the other Philistine commanders did not trust David.
it was also the best decision to go back and not fight against Israel because they went back home to find that the Amalekite had gone on a raid and taken their family captive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 28</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 10:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/28/</guid>
      <description>1SA 28:16 mercy. Saul had become God&amp;rsquo;s 3nrmy and he also went to consult a medium
Related verses: 1 Samuel 28:16. See notes
1SA 28:16 God became Saul&amp;rsquo;s enemy because of disobedience in failing to execute judgement on the Amalekites
Related verses: 1 SAMUEL 28:16, 1 SAMUEL 28:18. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 26</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 09:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/26/</guid>
      <description>1SA 26:19 David&amp;rsquo;s worry was more of sharing in God&amp;rsquo;s inheritance and not serving other gods
Related verses: 1 Samuel 26:19. See notes
1SA 26:11 in honour of God. if David had killed Saul, he would have been an illegitimate king and would have died in the hands of Absalom.
David sought God&amp;rsquo;s glory rather than personal fame and glory
Related verses: 1 Samuel 26:11. See notes
1SA 26:10 David&amp;rsquo;s word came to pass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 25</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 18:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/25/</guid>
      <description>1SA 25:31 Abigail was indeed sent by God. she knew David will become King soon and she spoke sensibly. preventing David from shedding blood without cause and she said HE SHOULD REMEMBER HER
Related verses: 1 Samuel 25:31. See notes
1SA 25:17 Ready to be destroyed because of foolishness, wickedness and not listening to instructions
Related verses: 1 Samuel 25:17. See notes
1SA 25:15 David was a shepherd. he had the skills and definitely also protect other people&amp;rsquo;s sheep</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 24</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 14:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/24/</guid>
      <description>1SA 24:8 There&amp;rsquo;s very much in common with ancient Israel and the Yorubas. it might be possible that the Yorubas maintained a lot of the cultural aspect of long ago. As I read the Bible more and more it becomes more apparent
Related verses: 1 Samuel 24:8. See notes
1SA 24:5 Quick to repent. has a working conscience
Related verses: 1 Samuel 24:5. See notes
1SA 24:2 3000 best fighters just for David and 600 men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 23</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 23:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/23/</guid>
      <description>1SA 23:17 What a friend. God please give me the mindset of Jonathan. A faithful friend
Related verses: 1 Samuel 23:17. See notes
1SA 23:14 God was David&amp;rsquo;s protector. he did not allow his enemy to catch him.
God deliver me from my enemies
Related verses: 1 Samuel 23:14. See notes
1SA 23:28 Saul was willing to take all or most of his armies in pursuit of a man you her than him to kill him but he left God&amp;rsquo;s sheep vulnerable and unprotected against Philistines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 22</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 05:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/22/</guid>
      <description>1SA 22:22 David accepted blame even for his indirect actions. he didn&amp;rsquo;t put the blame on Doeg or Saul
Related verses: 1 Samuel 22:22. See notes
1SA 22:19 What Saul didn&amp;rsquo;t do to the Amalejites, he did to the city of the priests of God at Nob even though they were all innocent. Saul has now gone very far
Related verses: 1 Samuel 22:19. See notes
1SA 22:15 it wasn&amp;rsquo;t the first time David enquired of the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 21</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 08:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/21/</guid>
      <description>1SA 21:12 David had a beard as mentioned in this chapter that gecdrooled on it. he also had hair as mentioned in the two previous chapter when his wife Michal used goat&amp;rsquo;s hair on an household idol to disguise that as David when Saul sent his messengers to kill him at his house
Related verses: 1 Samuel 21:12. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 20</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 08:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/20/</guid>
      <description>1SA 20:31 God had already said through Samuel that Saul&amp;rsquo;s throne would not be established but Saul is still forcing it by his own strength and might but God&amp;rsquo;s words would never be thwarted
Related verses: 1 Samuel 20:31. See notes
1SA 20:22 The arrow signifies Saul&amp;rsquo;s onslaught against David. if it&amp;rsquo;s beyond him then it means Saul really intrds to kill David as we will see later on
Related verses: 1 Samuel 20:22.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 19</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 07:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/19/</guid>
      <description>1SA 19:20 The spirit of God came on these laymen who had been sent to kill David and they also prophesied
Related verses: 1 Samuel 19:20. See notes
1SA 19:23 Saul was determined to terminate David&amp;rsquo;s life and he sent soldiers after Soldiers to kill David when he fled to Samuel at Ramah. The soldiers ended up prophesying until he himself came and he also prophesied such that he lay naked prophesying till night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 18</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 06:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/18/</guid>
      <description>1SA 18:30 David acted wisely and became successful in everything he did. David is constantly mentioned as bring wise and having the presence of God
Related verses: 1 Samuel 18:30. See notes
1SA 18:27 David did more than required. the foreskin of the Philistine was proof of tger8desth or how can one circumcize 200 living enemy Philistines while they are alive without giving a serious fight.
Saul required 100 but David brought 200 foreskins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 17</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 07:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/17/</guid>
      <description>1SA 17:37 this should be my confession. if God has saved me many times from death, he will surely rescue me whenever I am in trouble
Related verses: 1 Samuel 17:37. See notes
1SA 17:18 David had been anointed as king for war but was still feeding the sheep and delivering cheese. he was still an errand boy until the Holy Spirit moved his father to send him on delivery. this marked a milestone for his future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 15</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 21:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/15/</guid>
      <description>1SA 15:12 God gave the Victory but Saul took the glory
Related verses: 1 Samuel 15:12. See notes
1SA 15:9 The sin here is that they consciously disobeyed God by destroying every bad thing but left the best. Willful selection. Saul spared Agag because he wanted it to boost his ego since Agag has become his prisoner of war.
For those who were with Saul, he wanted to be the respected king among them by giving them the best of the spoils of war but the booty was God&amp;rsquo;s because everything was to be devoted to destruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 14</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 08:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/14/</guid>
      <description>1SA 14:45 Jonathan brought a victory. they said he worked with God and that saved his life from Saul&amp;rsquo;s foolish oath
Related verses: 1 Samuel 14:45. See notes
1SA 14:3 Ahijah was Eli&amp;rsquo;s grandchild whose mother died when she heard news of the ark taken by the Philistines. He was probably an elder brother to Ichabod and the son of Phinehas
Related verses: 1 Samuel 14:3. See notes
1SA 14:7 Nothing prevents the Lord from saving by few or by many as we saw with Gideon, with Jonathan and with Saul</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 10</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 10:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/10/</guid>
      <description>1SA 10:27 it&amp;rsquo;s an insult not to bring a gift before the appointed ruler. they treated Saul with contempt (God&amp;rsquo;s choice)
Related verses: 1 Samuel 10:27. See notes
1SA 10:6 To be changed into another man is for one&amp;rsquo;s heart to be changed. God can change me heart.
Related verses: 1 Samuel 10:6, 1 Samuel 10:9. See notes
1SA 10:6 After the spirit comes upon me, I will prophesy, be changed into another person, my mindset will be transformed to think in God&amp;rsquo;s line of direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 9</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 10:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/9/</guid>
      <description>1SA 9:19 A Seer(prophet) like Samuel could see what&amp;rsquo;s in the mind of a person through the power of the Holy Spirit
Related verses: 1 Samuel 9:19. See notes
1SA 9:27 I don&amp;rsquo;t know why Saul was anointed in secret. David was first anointed in the midst of his brothers. Solomon was anointed in the chambers. Jehu was also anointed by one of the sons of the prophet after being commanded by Elijah and he was anointed in the inner room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 08:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/5/</guid>
      <description>1SA 5:7 God would not be manipulated to act on my behalf especially when I am living a sinful lifestyle. neither would God share his glory with any other. The ark of God was placed before Dagon to show Dagon&amp;rsquo;s superiority but God struck Dagon and he fell before the ark thus God was showing his superiority.
God also struck the Philistine cities with plagues as he did in Egypt. he first struck their gods then their 5 lords, then the people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 18:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/4/</guid>
      <description>1SA 4:11 there was even more killed when the ark was brought than when it wasn&amp;rsquo;t present
Related verses: 1 Samuel 4:11. See notes
1SA 4:9 The Philistines did not want to become slaves to the Hebrews. They encouraged themselves and fought and got the victory.
the ark was a mere symbol of God&amp;rsquo;s presence but not his presence. The ark was with the Israelites but God&amp;rsquo;s presence wasn&amp;rsquo;t there</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 3</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 08:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/3/</guid>
      <description>1SA 3:10 the Lord actually came and stood even though Samuel did nit see anybody. where the voice of God is, his presence is also there.
Related verses: 1 Samuel 3:10. See notes
1SA 3:18 Not even a sign of remorse or repentance. Eli was not even bothered anymore. &amp;ldquo;I am an old man. I will die soon. the children should face their consequences, afterall when I am gone, there will be nothing to worry about&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 31</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 08:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/31/</guid>
      <description>1SA 31:12 Irrespective of how rebellious or ungodly you are, doing good in the past will help you one day. Saul had previously helped the inhabitants of Jabesh-Gilead when Nahash the ammonite came against them.
This time, they repaid Saul&amp;rsquo;s kindness by giving him a decent burial instead of a shameful one by getting his body from the wall of Beth-Shan (the Philistines intention was for people passing by to Mock Saul and Israel as people passed by) and hail their gods</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 16</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 01:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/16/</guid>
      <description>1SA 16:22 The anointing gives you favour before men of high authority but you have to serve your way to the top in the kingdom of God
Related verses: 1 SAMUEL 16:22. See notes
1SA 16:13 After anointing comes the spirit of the Lord upon a person with power for warfare
Related verses: 1 SAMUEL 16:13, ISAIAH 61:1, LUKE 4:18. See notes
1SA 16:4 Obedience to God and commitment to him rises you above ordinary men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 13</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 07:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/13/</guid>
      <description>1SA 13:13 Even though it was true Saul waited the seven days he was commanded to, if he had waited longer and not allowed fear to overcome him, his kingdom would have been established forever.
If I was Saul I probably would have done the same except if I knew that it was wrong to sacrifice when you are not anointed to stand in the office of a priest. Lord give me wisdom to know the way to go, the things to do and the steps to take.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 12</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 06:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/12/</guid>
      <description>1SA 12:20 After every evil thing has been done, God still forgives and wants us to get back to him. Serving him with all our heart
Related verses: 1 SAMUEL 12:20. See notes
1SA 12:17 The Israelites were afraid. They were led by fear to request a king because Nahash (serpent) the ammonite king besieged them.
Sometimes, we seek for another source of help and leadership other than God. God considers this evil</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 11</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 07:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/11/</guid>
      <description>1SA 11:1 Nahash meaning Serpent, an ammonite king of the descendants of lot went and besieged Jabesh in Israel, until Saul acted like kings do and brought the people together in unity, nothing could be done. God gave them victory over Nahash.
When we believers gather together in unity, the serpent goes down and his hordes are scatttered
Related verses: 1 Samuel 11:1. See notes
1SA 11:13 Saul here was still humble and attributing things (victory) to God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 8</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 23:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/8/</guid>
      <description>1SA 8:20 God allows us to do something even if the intention for doing it wasn&amp;rsquo;t right. Although he warns us of the consequence but when we reject God&amp;rsquo;s counsel, we fall into error
Related verses: 1 Samuel 8:19-20. See notes
1SA 8:4 When Samuel was old, he appointed his two sons to be judges in Beersheba but they didn&amp;rsquo;t walk in the ways of God. They were corrupt so the elders of Israel demanded for a King.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 7</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 22:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/7/</guid>
      <description>1SA 7:3 It&amp;rsquo;s our job to remove the foreign gods among us and serve him only and he will see to it that we are rescued from the hands of the enemy
Related verses: 1 SAMUEL 7:3. See notes
1SA 7:2 The ark was in Kiriath-Jearim in Gibeah probably the one in the territory of Judah
Related verses: 1 SAMUEL 7:2. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1SA 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 07:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/1sa/6/</guid>
      <description>1SA 6:19 David was probably about 10 years when this happened from looking at the next chapter. Saul was 42 years older than David. Saul must have been 52 years when this happened. That would mean he was already reigning 12 years on the throne of Israel when this happened. 3 years later, David was anointed king and fought with Goliath
Related verses: 1 Samuel 6:19. See notes
1SA 6:19 In time of harvest, celebration there was mourning because some men of Beth-Shemesh had become familiar with God to the point of looking into the ark and God killed them for their error and lack of reverence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
