<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NEH on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/neh/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NEH on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 23:28:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/neh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NEH 13</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 23:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/13/</guid>
      <description>NEH 13:26 God so loved Solomon that he changed Solomon&amp;rsquo;s name to Jedidiah. Unfortunately, Solomon&amp;rsquo;s heart was turned away because Solomon married foreign pagan women who turned his heart away from God.
Related verses: NEHEMIAH 13:26. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEH 8</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/8/</guid>
      <description>NEH 8:10 There is a time to work and there is a time to celebrate. As Christians too, we should have a joint mass celebration because we serve the living God.
Maybe we should have a Christian parade with banners on the word of God and how God has been good to us
Related verses: NEHEMIAH 8:10. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEH 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 00:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/6/</guid>
      <description>NEH 6:16 Wow I&amp;rsquo;ve come to love Nehemiah. He always thought about God in all he was doing. He never gave up in the face of adversity. When the people was discouraged, he encouraged them in the Lord. When his life was in danger, he never feared but trusted in God.
Finally he attributed completing the rebuilding of the walls of Jerusalem to help from God.
While many could have said, we used some genius minds, technical capabilities and other big words and in the end our efforts paid off, Nehemiah attributed things to God and didn&amp;rsquo;t take credit for it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEH 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 08:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/5/</guid>
      <description>NEH 5:19 Everything Nehemiah did is apparent that he loved God and his people. He did all he could to prevent tauntings from the enemies of the Jews.
He sacrificed many benefits for the good of his people. A good leader can be known by how much he is willing to sacrifice his comfort for the things of God first then his people.
This characteristic is lacking in the part of many leaders of nations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEH 4</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 07:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/4/</guid>
      <description>NEH 4:20 OUR GOD WILL FIGHT FOR US
What a leader serving a great God
Related verses: NEHEMIAH 4:20. See notes
NEH 4:14 When you are discouraged, that is the time never to give up but recount all of God&amp;rsquo;s goodness in times past. Nehemiah used that to encourage his people (Nehemiah 4:14).
David before he became king when against Goliath wasn&amp;rsquo;t discouraged or afraid of his life but he simply encouraged himself by speaking out what God has done for him in times past (1 Samuel 17:37)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEH 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 07:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/neh/1/</guid>
      <description>NEH 1:6 One of the first prayers I used to pray after I had gotten saved years ago. Good to read this again.
Thank you God for how far you have brought me
Related verses: NEHEMIAH 1:5-11. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
