<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ISA on Quiet time notes</title>
    <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/isa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ISA on Quiet time notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 07:37:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quiettime.netlify.app/book/isa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ISA 14</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 07:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/14/</guid>
      <description>ISA 14:11 Sheol (Hades) or the place of the dead is below the earth according to spiritual geography. It shows that when men die they go down immediately. Jesus also died and went to hell because the scripture says that he went and preached to the dead.
Lazarus and the rich man was also in hell. The difference is that Lazarus was in paradise whereas the rich man was in hell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 65</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/65/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 06:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/65/</guid>
      <description>ISA 65:20 It&amp;rsquo;s meant to be a minimum of 100 years old. Anything short of that will be thought of as a curse according to the scriptures here
Related verses: Isaiah 65:20. See notes
ISA 65:2 Following are the thought and intention of my heart can be dangerous if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t align with the word and will if God. This is the reason everything I do and think of must be subjected to the word of God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 63</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/63/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 09:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/63/</guid>
      <description>ISA 63:5 Everyone has gone their own way and no I&amp;rsquo;ve was listening to the prophets warning. There was so much idolatry and bloodshed a new the time of judgement was at hand.
Related verses: Isaiah 63:5. See notes
ISA 63:1 Crimson-stained garment, symbolic of blood and symbolic of victory over the enemy.
Related verses: Isaiah 63:1. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 62</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/62/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 09:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/62/</guid>
      <description>ISA 62:7 We can continue to call on God such that he is forced to give a response
Related verses: Isaiah 62:7, Luke 18:1-9. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 60</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/60/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 10:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/60/</guid>
      <description>ISA 60:22 The nation Israel began with two old couples and the wife was barren but it became a nation through which salvation came.
It will get be more glorious in the future especially in the second coming of Jesus.
Related verses: Isaiah 60:22. See notes
ISA 60:6 Prophecy to what finally happened when Jesus was born. Wise men from the east brought Gold, Frankincense and myrrh
Related verses: 1 Kings 10:2, Isaiah 60:6, Matthew 2:1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 59</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/59/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 08:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/59/</guid>
      <description>ISA 59:17 The Lord&amp;rsquo;s armour Vs the believer&amp;rsquo;s armour
Related verses: Isaiah 59:17, Ephesians 6:14-15. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 58</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/58/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 08:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/58/</guid>
      <description>ISA 58:5 Fasting is a means of humbling myself. It should also be a time to mourn for my sins and produce a repentant heart (poor in Spirit)
It looks like this fasting was done on the Sabbath because it was the only day that God did not permit work.
Fasting makes my voice heard. Fasting is not just about depriving the body of food even though it&amp;rsquo;s a means of starving the flesh to stuff the Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 51</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/51/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 05:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/51/</guid>
      <description>ISA 51:2 The blessings of the Lord makes rich. It always increase
Related verses: Genesis 1:28, Proverbs 10:22, Isaiah 51:2. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 50</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/50/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 05:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/50/</guid>
      <description>ISA 50:1 We go into slavery because of sins, injustice and wickedness and away from God&amp;rsquo;s presence because of transgression (breaking God&amp;rsquo;s law)
Related verses: Isaiah 50:1. See notes
ISA 50:5 Suffering of the messiah prophesied long ago by Isaiah the Prophet.
Jesus had the tongue of disciples that&amp;rsquo;s why people were amazed at his teaching and his words could comfort people.
Related verses: Isaiah 50:4-7, Matthew 26:67-68. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 45</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/45/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 04:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/45/</guid>
      <description>ISA 45:7 God created darkness and disaster but forms light and peace
Related verses: Isaiah 45:7. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 43</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/43/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 10:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/43/</guid>
      <description>ISA 43:2 Israel passed through the waters if the red sea and Shadrach, Meshach and Abednego was put in the flames of Babylon
Related verses: Isaiah 43:2. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 42</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/42/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 10:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/42/</guid>
      <description>ISA 42:1 Moses was the deliverer from Egypt, Cyrus was the deliverer from Babylon, Christ is the deliverer from sin and the world.
Related verses: Isaiah 42:1. See notes
ISA 42:1 God puts his Spirit in those he delights.
Related verses: Isaiah 42:1. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 41</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 10:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/41/</guid>
      <description>ISA 41:25 Cyrus the Great was a believer of the God of Israel
Related verses: Isaiah 41:25. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 40</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 10:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/40/</guid>
      <description>ISA 40:29 When weary, I need strength that comes from God. When tired, I need power
Related verses: Isaiah 40:29, Isaiah 40:31. See notes
ISA 40:12 Similarities in both verses and Jesus fulfilled the calming of the storm and rebuking the wind. He also walked on water
Related verses: Proverbs 30:4-5, Isaiah 40:12. See notes
ISA 40:31 Prayer is waiting on God. It gives strength
Related verses: Isaiah 40:31. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 32</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/32/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 09:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/32/</guid>
      <description>ISA 32:17 The seed of divine wisdom produces the fruit of righteousness and this also brings forth peace
Related verses: Isaiah 32:17, James 3:18. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 31</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 11:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/31/</guid>
      <description>ISA 31:1 By the arm of flesh shall no man prevail. Assyrian was conquering nations and as small nations were taking cover for protection in Egypt under Pharaoh Shabako, Israel was also tempted to do the same and God was warning them but they didn&amp;rsquo;t listen and neither did they want to repent of idolatry.
Related verses: 1 Samuel 2:9, Isaiah 31:1, Jeremiah 17:5. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 27</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 04:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/27/</guid>
      <description>ISA 27:1 An answer and a confirmation to a prayer. I just need to be patient and wait for the day God will act
Related verses: Isaiah 27:1. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 6</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 14:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/6/</guid>
      <description>ISA 6:8 Before Isaiah was commissioned, his sins had to be purged with burning coals from the altar
Related verses: Isaiah 6:7-8. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 11</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 15:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/11/</guid>
      <description>ISA 11:2 The woman personified as wisdom is the Holy Spirit. The spirit of counsel, wisdom, understanding, power, knowledge as mentioned in Isaiah.
wisdom (The Holy Spirit) can provide everything I need. this wisdom personified as a woman was given to Jesus in full measure as seen in Isaiah 11:2.
the fruit of wisdom is better than silver or gold. the fruits of wisdom is love, joy, peace, patience, kindness, goodness and faithfulness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 48</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/48/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 07:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/48/</guid>
      <description>ISA 48:18 Obedience to God is the key that unlocks everything else
Related verses: ISAIAH 48:18-19. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 37</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/37/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 09:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/37/</guid>
      <description>ISA 37:11 First Sennacherib tries to discourage the people by telling them not to trust in their King Hezekiah because the enemy goes or the head. When he realised that Hezekiah was unmoved, then he tries to find the source of Hezekiah?s strength and when he realised his confidence was in God, he tries to persuade Hezekiah not to trust in God.
Do not let Hezekiah deceive you &amp;hellip; (in chapter 36) Do not let your God deceive you</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 36</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/36/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 09:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/36/</guid>
      <description>ISA 36:20 Those are the gods of other lands who can neither see, talk, walk but we serve a living God is is high, mighty, powerful and glorious who can never be compared to anything else
Related verses: ISAIAH 36:20. See notes
ISA 36:19 Dangerous and proud speaking. The enemy uses intimidation, deception and worldly pleasures making us think what we have is not good enough. He tries to lure us away from the promised land</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 35</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/35/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 07:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/35/</guid>
      <description>ISA 35:4 The coming of the Lord Jesus now fulfilled
Related verses: ISAIAH 35:4-6. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 26</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 09:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/26/</guid>
      <description>ISA 26:3 There is peace and there is perfect peace. This can only be given by the prince of peace.
Thesaurus defines peace as freedom of the mind from annoyance, distraction, anxiety, obsession etc.
We can only achieve perfect peace when our mind is focused on Jesus and not of the things of the world. There is always tribulation in the world. We live in a fast paced world that tries us out but focusing on Jesus helps us to discard unnecessary problems that can occur with a mind focused on the world, its fleeting pleasures, fame and glory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 5</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 01:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/5/</guid>
      <description>ISA 5:13 Lack of knowledge of God produces the lack of the fear of God and this causes us to go into captivity because we do not know how mighty and powerful our God is. Ignorance is truly a deadly disease.
Related verses: ISAIAH 5:13. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 1</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 05:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/1/</guid>
      <description>ISA 1:26 The change comes with the judges and counsellors. (The leaders) and those in authority
Related verses: ISAIAH 1:26. See notes
ISA 1:11 To obey is better than sacrifice and to hearken than the fat of rams. Obedience and repentance is what God wants and not some &amp;ldquo;do this do that ritual because that can easily replace obedience and repentance&amp;rdquo;.
Related verses: ISAIAH 1:11. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 61</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/61/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 01:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/61/</guid>
      <description>ISA 61:1 After anointing comes the spirit of the Lord upon a person with power for warfare
Related verses: 1 SAMUEL 16:13, ISAIAH 61:1, LUKE 4:18. See notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA 64</title>
      <link>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/64/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 06:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quiettime.netlify.app/notes/isa/64/</guid>
      <description>ISA 64:6 It&amp;rsquo;s impossible to attain righteousness by our good works. If it was so, how many good works must we do? How about other people who have sinned but not have the opportunity to start any good words whilst isolated in prison. They are damned.
If God&amp;rsquo;s standard of righteousness is based on good works then who is the man whose good works will be the dividing line between enough good works and not enough good works.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
